<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<hints>
 <hint name="av.hints.1"><![CDATA[If you place a decoration next to a passenger building it generates more passengers.]]></hint>
 <hint name="av.hints.2"><![CDATA[The little hearts on a friends tag are called buddy points.]]></hint>
 <hint name="av.hints.3"><![CDATA[The WonderQuicky is more than 3 times better than the normal Rama-XS-Quicky.]]></hint>
 <hint name="av.hints.4"><![CDATA[You can also click on the Luggage Depot to open the lucky luggage.]]></hint>
 <hint name="av.hints.5"><![CDATA[Try out “All You Can Quickservice” if you know you will send a lot of planes today.]]></hint>
 <hint name="av.hints.6"><![CDATA[The only way to get the Rama-Falcon is by collecting plane parts in the lucky luggage.]]></hint>
 <hint name="av.hints.7"><![CDATA[You can get the Skyscraper only from the lucky luggage.]]></hint>
 <hint name="av.hints.8"><![CDATA[Check your collection from time to time to see what souvenirs you’re missing.]]></hint>
 <hint name="av.hints.9"><![CDATA[Every country can drop 3 different souvenirs. Fly to countries you need souvenirs from.]]></hint>
 <hint name="av.hints.10"><![CDATA[Small planes are ideal for collecting many souvenirs.]]></hint>
 <hint name="av.hints.11"><![CDATA[Hold the left mouse button to drag the map around.]]></hint>
 <hint name="av.hints.12"><![CDATA[Zoom in and out using the mouse wheel.]]></hint>
 <hint name="av.hints.13"><![CDATA[Passengers stay at your airport for just 5 days, so don't forget to send them home on time!]]></hint>
 <hint name="av.hints.14"><![CDATA[When you service a buddy’s cargo plane you get some of the cargo from its home country.]]></hint>
 <hint name="av.hints.15"><![CDATA[Cobblestone plates can be flipped, they just look the same.]]></hint>
 <hint name="av.hints.16"><![CDATA[Daily goals depend on your level and can be a significant booster for your progress.]]></hint>
 <hint name="av.hints.17"><![CDATA[To service helicopters all you need is a Helipad.]]></hint>
 <hint name="av.hints.18"><![CDATA[The same country will always provide wares for the same shop category.]]></hint>
 <hint name="av.hints.19"><![CDATA[Every second level a shop needs one additional ware to produce a better version of its products.]]></hint>
 <hint name="av.hints.20"><![CDATA[On its highest level a shop needs 4 wares to produce products.]]></hint>
 <hint name="av.hints.21"><![CDATA[High level shops are harder to manage, but the profit you gain is a lot higher as well.]]></hint>
 <hint name="av.hints.22"><![CDATA[If you are missing some wares you can buy them in the warehouse pop-up.]]></hint>
 <hint name="av.hints.23"><![CDATA[For every consecutive day you log in you get more free spins on the lucky luggage.]]></hint>
 <hint name="av.hints.24"><![CDATA[1930’s planes don’t bring you back coins but a lot of experience points.]]></hint>
 <hint name="av.hints.25"><![CDATA[Passenger buildings in storage don’t produce passengers.]]></hint>
 <hint name="av.hints.26"><![CDATA[Refill your shops before landing planes to maximize your revenue.]]></hint>
 <hint name="av.hints.28"><![CDATA[Ramacopters generate more aircoins than comparable normal planes.]]></hint>
 <hint name="av.hints.29"><![CDATA[As soon as you have a warehouse you can start collecting all sorts of wares by sending cargo planes.]]></hint>
 <hint name="av.hints.30"><![CDATA[Buildings can be rotated 90 degrees with the “Flip” tool in your storage.]]></hint>
 <hint name="av.hints.31"><![CDATA[All shops have specific characteristics which you can look up in the shop or storage mouse over.]]></hint>
 <hint name="av.hints.32"><![CDATA[You can upgrade your hangar and warehouse capacity by clicking on the building on your airport.]]></hint>
 <hint name="av.hints.33"><![CDATA[Completing goals can give you experience, coins, planes, passengers, buildings or building upgrades.]]></hint>
 <hint name="av.hints.34"><![CDATA[Many items can be bought in the shop for Aircash before you reach the necessary level.]]></hint>
 <hint name="av.hints.35"><![CDATA[Quickservicing can be a great timesaver when sending and servicing large planes.]]></hint>
 <hint name="av.hints.36"><![CDATA[Out of Aircoins or passengers? You can trade Aircash for Aircoins or passengers in the shop's “Specials” category.]]></hint>
 <hint name="av.hints.37"><![CDATA[Need more space for your airport? You can buy map extentions in the shop's “Specials” category.]]></hint>
 <hint name="av.hints.38"><![CDATA[You can buy different backgrounds in the shop's “Specials” category.]]></hint>
 <hint name="av.hints.39"><![CDATA[Hallow-scream through the clouds in Skyrama!]]></hint>
</hints>
