<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<language>
 <category name="av.goal">
  <item name="av.goals.tooltip.main"><![CDATA[Main goal]]></item>
  <item name="av.goals.tooltip.daily"><![CDATA[Daily goal]]></item>
  <item name="av.goals.tooltip.story"><![CDATA[Story goal]]></item>
  <item name="av.goals.tooltip.world"><![CDATA[Visit every country!]]></item>
  <item name="av.finishGoal.message"><![CDATA[Finish goal]]></item>
  <item name="av.requirements.text.default"><![CDATA[Requirements:]]></item>
  <item name="av.requirements.text.mediumPlanes"><![CDATA[Required for sending medium planes:]]></item>
  <item name="av.requirements.text.heliCopter"><![CDATA[Required for sending ramacopters:]]></item>
  <item name="av.requirements.text.seaPlanes"><![CDATA[Required for sending sea planes:]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.0.name"><![CDATA[Land Your First Flight]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.0.hint"><![CDATA[Welcome to SkyRama!  My name is Fiona, your air traffic controller and mentor. I will guide you through a brief 8-step tutorial to help you learn the basics. Let's begin with landing your first flight... Click on the radar to open your flight dashboard, then click on the flight waiting to land.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.0.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Well done! You just landed your first flight and completed the first step of our tutorial. Although this flight was sent by a helper you will soon be landing planes sent by your own Buddies.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.0.LandPlane.name"><![CDATA[Land {number} CashCow(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.1.name"><![CDATA[Place Your First Bay]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.1.hint"><![CDATA[Passenger planes require servicing bays. I have put a free bay in your storage, ready for placing... Click the storage on your dashboard, then click on the small bay. Click again to place it.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.1.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Well done! You just placed your first bay and completed the second step of our tutorial. Bays are essential for servicing incoming and outgoing planes. The more bays you place, the more planes you can service at once.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.1.PlaceBay.name"><![CDATA[Place {number} small bay(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.2.name"><![CDATA[Service Your First Plane]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.2.hint"><![CDATA[All planes require some form of servicing. Completing a service chain brings all types of rewards... Keep clicking on the plane to fully service it and collect your rewards.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.2.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Well done! You just serviced your first plane and earned yourself some aircoin. These are essential resources for developing your economy.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.2.ReturnPlane.name"><![CDATA[Service {number} Rama-XS-Quickie]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.3.name"><![CDATA[Buy Your First Plane]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.3.hint"><![CDATA[If you want to send your own flights you need to own some planes... Click the store, then click on the Rama-XS-Quickie to buy it. It will be added to your hangar.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.3.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Well done! You just bought your first plane and reached the halfway mark of our tutorial. You need space in your hangar to buy planes. There are many types of planes in SkyRama, so be careful to check what kind of advantages and costs they offer.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.3.BuyPlane.19.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} Rama-XS-Quickie]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.4.name"><![CDATA[Send Your First Plane]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.4.hint"><![CDATA[You're ready to send off your own plane for the first time... Click on flightmap and 'send new flight', then select your plane, country, and buddy. Your plane will appear outside your hangar - keep clicking until it takes off.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.4.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Well done! You just sent your plane on its fledgling flight, it will return in 5 minutes. Sending your own flights costs passengers but you will make aircoins when they return.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.4.SendPlane.19.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-XS-Quickie]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.5.name"><![CDATA[Instant Service Your Plane]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.5.hint"><![CDATA[Waiting for a flight to be serviced can be time consuming and we are busy people. Why not shortcut the process? It only costs 1 AirCash to instantly service a plane... Click on the top left icon that appears above your plane, this is the instant service shortcut.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.5.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Well done! You just instant serviced your first plane. It saves you time and gives you all your bonuses in an instant. This is especially useful with slower planes that can take much longer to service.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.5.QuickStartPlane.name"><![CDATA[Instant Service a Plane.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.6.name"><![CDATA[Setup Your Passengers I]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.6.hint"><![CDATA[You need passengers to keep your own planes flying. Passengers are collected from special buildings, such as the small terminal... Click on the shop's passenger buildings, then buy and place the small terminal.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.6.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Well done! You just established your passenger flow. This and other buildings generate passengers. You know when a passenger generating building is full because the passenger icon appears above it. Hovering your cursor over a passenger building will give you an update on how many passengers it contains.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.6.PlaceTerminal.1.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} small terminal(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.6.ReturnPlane.name"><![CDATA[Return {number} Rama-XS-Quickie]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.7.name"><![CDATA[Setup Your Passengers II]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.7.hint"><![CDATA[Our last step in the tutorial. The small terminal is probably full by now. You should try collecting the passengers. A passenger icon appears above the small terminal when it is full and ready for collection.... Hover over the passenger icon to add the passengers to your total.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.7.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Well done! The more decorations and passenger buildings you own, the quicker you can collect your passengers... You are now finished with the tutorial and can start running the airport as you like but keep your eye out for goals - they will pop up from time to time. Our goals help guide your progression and provide very useful and exclusive rewards.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.7.GetPassengers.name"><![CDATA[Collect Passengers]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.8.name"><![CDATA[Run Your Airport I]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.8.hint"><![CDATA[Get used to your airport by sending flights]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.8.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Well done! I reckon you need more room in your hangar. Normally this kind of upgrade costs Air Cash but I'm giving you a hangar upgrade for free, meaning you have space for 2 more planes.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.8.SendPlane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Plane(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.8.GetPassengers.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} Passenger(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.10.name"><![CDATA[Expand Your Air-Side]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.10.hint"><![CDATA[Your airport needs to grow to become successful. Invest in some extra bays to help it develop... Look in the store and get spending. I have a very special reward waiting for you.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.10.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Well done! You are ready to handle more flights. The next step is to learn how to send cargo planes.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.10.BuyBay.1.name"><![CDATA[Place {number} small bay(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.10.SendPlane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Plane(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.125.name"><![CDATA[Visit Your Friends]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.125.hint"><![CDATA[You will have to build up a lot of relationships to make you airport really important. If you visit a friend you can help them out collecting passengers!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.125.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Well done! Did you recognize that you also earned passengers by helping out your friend? Go on visiting other airports if you are low on passengers.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.125.SendPlane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.401.name"><![CDATA[Emergency!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.401.hint"><![CDATA[Our terminal's toilets are broken. We need some rest-rooms to cover the down time! Try to purchase additional rest-rooms as soon as possible!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.401.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[What a great deal! One of our customers was so relieved that he donated his old 1930's Racer!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.401.PlaceLandsideBuilding.92.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} rest-room(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.309.name"><![CDATA[Decorate your airport]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.309.hint"><![CDATA[If you want to attract more passengers to your airport, decorate it! Why don't you try some of those nice looking flowers?]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.309.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Great! If you place decorations next to buildings even more passengers will come to your airport!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.309.SendPlane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.309.BuyLandsideBuilding.44.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} flowerbox]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.400.name"><![CDATA[South America]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.400.hint"><![CDATA[I would love to fly to South America. Can you help me out?]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.400.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Wonderful! South America is such a beautiful place! I would love to go shopping in Rio.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.400.SendPlane.sa.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to South America]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.400.GetPassengers.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} Passengers]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.402.name"><![CDATA[1930s Racer Planes]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.402.hint"><![CDATA[I think I should test our new baby: this great old 1930s Racer plane - the Hughes.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.402.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Wonderful! Let's get more of those!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.402.GetPassengers.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} passengers]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.402.SendPlane.32.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Hughes Racer]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.404.name"><![CDATA[Souvenirs]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.404.hint"><![CDATA[Did you realise that incoming planes drop souvenirs? Different countries, different souvenirs! Collect some of them.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.404.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Great job, it's that easy to make friends happy! Just bring some souvenirs back from your travels!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.404.CollectSouvenir.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} souvenirs]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.405.name"><![CDATA[A friendly turn]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.405.hint"><![CDATA[A world famous airport needs a lot of communication. Let's visit a friend and send another one a message.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.405.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Congratulations. Don't forget to take care of you friends.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.405.SendPlane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.405.SendPlane.34.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Flyby(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.406.name"><![CDATA[Europe]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.406.hint"><![CDATA[I would love to fly to Europe. Can you help me out?]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.406.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Wonderful! Europe is such a beautiful place! I would love to wander along the boulevards of Paris, and go clubbing in Berlin.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.406.SendPlane.eu.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s) to europe]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.300.name"><![CDATA[Tutorial: Setup Your Cargo Bay]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.300.hint"><![CDATA[If we want our airport to be highly profitable we will need some shops where our passengers can spend the rest of their holiday money. I’ll give you a quick introduction of everything we will need.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.300.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Great job! Cargo Bays are needed to service and send Cargo Planes. Next we will need a warehouse to store our goods. You can find your new warehouse in your storage.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.300.PlaceBay.13.name"><![CDATA[Place {number} Cargo Bay]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.301.name"><![CDATA[Tutorial: Setup Your Warehouse]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.301.hint"><![CDATA[In order to store all the cargo for our shops we will need a warehouse.  Shops get the cargo they need for their products from the warehouse so keep an eye on your stocks.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.301.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Perfect! Now that we have all we need to store wares let’s send our first cargo plane.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.301.PlaceWarehouse.3.name"><![CDATA[Place {number} Warehouse]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.302.name"><![CDATA[Tutorial: Get Your First Wares I]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.302.hint"><![CDATA[Now that we have a bay the next step is to send our new cargo plane to a country to get some wares. Select a country that sells flour and send your cargo plane there.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.302.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Nicely done! Next you have to land it.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.302.SendPlane.20.name"><![CDATA[Send Cargo plane]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.302.SendPlane.1047.name"><![CDATA[Send Cargo plane]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.303.name"><![CDATA[Tutorial: Get Your First Wares II]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.303.hint"><![CDATA[There! Our cargo plane is returning already, filled to the grim with flour. Let’s bring it down safely.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.303.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Good work!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.303.LandPlane.20.name"><![CDATA[Land Cargo Plane]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.303.LandPlane.1047.name"><![CDATA[Land Cargo Plane]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.304.name"><![CDATA[Tutorial: Collect Cargo]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.304.hint"><![CDATA[Now we have to store the flour in our warehouse. Just service the plane till the flour bag appears. By hovering over it you can than move it to your warehouse.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.304.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Very well. The wares from your plane are now stored safely in our warehouse. Take a look in your storage. You’ll find your first shop in there.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.304.GetCargo.1.name"><![CDATA[Collect Flour]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.305.name"><![CDATA[Tutorial: Your First Shop]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.305.hint"><![CDATA[Now that we have the wares in our warehouse it would be a pity to let them go to waste.  Time to get our first shop. Shops turn wares into products that can be sold to passengers.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.305.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Splendid! The burger-shop will produce burgers and sell them to arriving passenger planes.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.305.PlaceCargoshop.1.name"><![CDATA[Place Burger Shop]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.306.name"><![CDATA[Tutorial: Your First Customers]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.306.hint"><![CDATA[There are the first customers for our new shop! Every time you land a plane our shops will sell a certain amount of products.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.306.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[These passengers are now going to buy some burgers.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.306.LandPlane.37.name"><![CDATA[Land Plane]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.307.name"><![CDATA[Tutorial: Your First Sales]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.307.hint"><![CDATA[When you hover over the red shopping bag the passengers will start visiting our shops. If a shop made money there will be a coins symbol on top of it. Collect your money by hovering over the coin icon.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.307.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Excellent! You now know everything you need to manage your shops. If a shop sells enough products it will reach a higher level. Every level the one more ware is needed. So it will become more challenging to manage the shop but you will make more money with higher products as well.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.307.SellProducts.name"><![CDATA[Sell Products]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.308.name"><![CDATA[Tutorial: Manage Your Shop]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.308.hint"><![CDATA[Keep in mind that shops can only sell products if they are supplied with sufficient wares. If a shop ran out of wares it will have a red exclamation mark hovering over it. Click on the shop to refill it.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.308.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Great work! The shop will now produce burgers for the starving passengers.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.308.FillShop.1.name"><![CDATA[Refill Your Shop]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.11.name"><![CDATA[Setup Your Luggage Depot]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.11.hint"><![CDATA[Have you ever thought about the luggage? It's getting complicated we really need a Luggage Depot!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.11.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Well done! Our work is a lot easier now. Keep up the good work!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.11.PlaceTerminal.2.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} medium tower(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.11.PlaceLandsideBuilding.26.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} luggage depot(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.11.SendPlane.21.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-XS-Turbo]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.12.name"><![CDATA[Medium Hangar]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.12.hint"><![CDATA[You are already on your way to scaling up your airport, readying it to service bigger planes. Once you have a medium bay the airport association will reward you with a medium hangar.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.12.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Well done! You are now just a medium airstrip away from medium planes! Check your next Goal to finally be able to service medium planes.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.12.PlaceRunway.2.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} medium runway(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.12.BuyBay.3.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} medium bay(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.12.SendPlane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.12.SendPlane.32.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} 1930s Racer Hughes]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.123.name"><![CDATA[On the Runway]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.123.hint"><![CDATA[There is just this expensive medium airstrip missing. Lets visit some of our Buddies and service some planes maybe we can find a sponsor!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.123.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Well done! You now own all parts necessary for landing and servicing bigger planes.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.123.SendPlane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.123.SendPlane.21.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-XS-Turbo]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.13.name"><![CDATA[Scale Up Your Terminal]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.13.hint"><![CDATA[So far your Terminal has had a minimal impact but this is just the tip of the iceberg. I want you to scale up your terminal operations. Think big.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.13.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Well done! You now have a bigger terminal]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.13.SendPlane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.13.SendPlane.32.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} 1930s Racer Hughes]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.13.SendPlane.19.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-XS-Quickie]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.13.BuyExtension.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} map extention(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.13.BuyBay.4.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} medium terminal(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.29.name"><![CDATA[Scale Up Your Cargo-Shops]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.29.hint"><![CDATA[So far your shops have had a minimal impact but this is just the tip of the iceberg. I want you to scale up your cargo operations. Think big.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.29.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Well done! You now have a delicous, cake-baking pastry shop in your storage.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.29.BuyBay.14.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} medium cargo-bay(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.29.SendPlane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Plane(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.29.SendPlane.27.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-M-Cargo]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.124.name"><![CDATA[Get used to medium cargo planes]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.124.hint"><![CDATA[To finally increase your income by selling lots of products to passengers you need to invest in medium cargo planes. Buy and send some!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.124.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Well done! You now have bigger cargo planes - that's the supply side taken care of. Keep your warehouse storage filled by sending lots of cargo planes to your Buddies.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.124.BuyWarehouse.2.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} medium cargo-bay(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.124.SendPlane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Plane(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.124.SendPlane.27.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-M-Cargo]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.124.SendPlane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Plane(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.30.name"><![CDATA[Max Your Airport Operations]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.30.hint"><![CDATA[Your airport is doing well but you need to pay attention to your Buddies and maximising your airport's current potential. Some hard graft will be required but you will get a handy bay as reward. Go grind!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.30.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Well done! You can find a medium bay in your storage. Soon your airport will be ready for the next stage in its evolution.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.30.SendPlane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.30.BuyExtension.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} map extension(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.30.SendPlane.29.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-M-SuperTurbo]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.31.name"><![CDATA[Run Your Airport II]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.31.hint"><![CDATA[Get used to your airport by servicing flights]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.31.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Perfect! Now let's focus on Passengers!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.31.ReturnPlane.name"><![CDATA[Return {number} CashCow(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.31.GetPassengers.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} Passenger(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.33.name"><![CDATA[Practice Makes Perfect]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.33.hint"><![CDATA[Get used to running your airport by sending and servicing planes]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.33.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Great, The more air traffic you achieve the more AirCoins you earn! The first step to max out your earnings is to establish flight-routes to all ressources needed!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.33.SendPlane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Plane(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.33.ReturnPlane.name"><![CDATA[Return {number} CashCow(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.32.name"><![CDATA[Setup Your Cargo I]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.32.hint"><![CDATA[If you want to earn money with your cargo-shops you need to supply the shop with goods by sending cargo planes. To send cargo planes properly, the airport needs a fuel depot.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.32.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Well done!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.32.BuyLandsideBuilding.20.name"><![CDATA[Place {number} small fuel depot(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.32.SendPlane.19.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-XS-Quickie]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.34.name"><![CDATA[Setup Your Cargo II]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.34.hint"><![CDATA[Fill up your warehouse storage by sending and servicing cargo flights.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.34.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Well done! Keep collecting cargo to produce more products!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.34.SendPlane.20.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-XS-Cargo]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.34.BuyLandsideBuilding.1.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} parking lot(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.35.name"><![CDATA[Try Out Medium Flights]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.35.hint"><![CDATA[Now it's time to play with some bigger toys. Try dispatching and servicing medium-sized planes.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.35.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Well done! Medium planes might cost a lot more, in terms of passengers and money, but the payoffs are much bigger.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.35.SendPlane.25.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-M-Turbo]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.35.ReturnPlane.25.name"><![CDATA[Return {number} Rama-M-Turbo]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.40.name"><![CDATA[Setup Your Weather Station]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.40.hint"><![CDATA[The Ramacopter agent told us that your airport will soon be advanced enough for Ramacopters! Get prepared by investing in a hi-tech weather station]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.40.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Wonderful!! One Step closer to Ramacopters, lets focus on our new Tasks!!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.40.SendPlane.27.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-M-Cargo]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.40.BuyLandsideBuilding.48.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} weather station(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.41.name"><![CDATA[Ramacopter Hangar]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.41.hint"><![CDATA[The Ramacopter agents only supply their machines to the best. Your airport needs to increase its size and profit to show you mean business.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.41.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Congratulations!! Your airport has qualified for the Ramacopter hangar! You can find it in your storage!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.41.SendPlane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.41.GetAirCoins.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} AirCoin(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.42.name"><![CDATA[Collect Important Equipment]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.42.hint"><![CDATA[We are missing important equipment for monitoring our airspace. Get collecting. Without it the Ramacopter agent will never take us seriously.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.42.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Nice! The Ramacopter agent is impressed by our recent progress. Not much longer, he says, and we qualify for Ramacopters!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.42.SendPlane.27.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-M-Cargo]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.42.CollectSouvenir.21.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} radar(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.42.CollectSouvenir.23.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} windsock(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.43.name"><![CDATA[Ramacopters Are Go!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.43.hint"><![CDATA[Finally! How exciting, it's time to fill the sky with your very own Ramacopter! Don't be shy - get yourself a Ramacopter and take off!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.43.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Nice job! From now on your airport is capable of servicing all types of Ramacopters, congratulations!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.43.SendPlane.2.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Ramacopter-Quickie]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.44.name"><![CDATA[Get Flight Buddies]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.44.hint"><![CDATA[It's time to think global. Try to build up new relationships and add new Buddies!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.44.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Make your zoo smell nice Great! Reaching out to Buddies enhances your world, you should keep expanding your airport's global network.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.44.SendPlane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.45.name"><![CDATA[Deepen Your Buddy Relations]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.45.hint"><![CDATA[Deepening ties with your Buddies is very important. Visit their airports, if you find the time, and send them some medium flights.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.45.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Well done! Remember - helping out Buddies will boost your bonuses.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.45.SendPlane.29.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-M-Super-Turbo]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.45.SendPlane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.45.SendPlane.19.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-XS-Quickie]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.45.SendPlane.2.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Ramacopter-Quickie]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.46.name"><![CDATA[Broaden Your Airport's Appeal]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.46.hint"><![CDATA[Although your airport has lots of public appeal, you could increase it further. Install a field where people can fly their kites. Providing recreation sites will boost your airport's passenger appeal. That can't be bad!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.46.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Good job! We should keep listening to visitors it's always good to get more passengers!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.46.BuyLandsideBuilding.58.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} kite-field(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.46.GetPassengers.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} passenger(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.47.name"><![CDATA[Establish Your Holiday Destinations]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.47.hint"><![CDATA[The holiday season is soon upon us. You had better build up our reputation in these destinations. Send some medium planes to greek and spanish airports.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.47.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Very good, you have established some nice routes for all that holiday traffic. Keep on sending planes!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.47.SendPlane.25.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} medium plane(s) to Greece]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.47.SendPlane.12.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} medium plane(s) to Spain]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.47.SendPlane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.48.name"><![CDATA[Send Out More Ramacopters]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.48.hint"><![CDATA[Safety comes first! To guarantee that our Ramacopter pilots have the best practise possible I'd suggest sending some Ramacopters.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.48.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Nice, our pilots seem to have total control over their Ramacopters now. Keep sending Ramacopters!!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.48.SendPlane.2.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Ramacopter-Quickie]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.49.name"><![CDATA[Perfect Your Ramacopter Services]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.49.hint"><![CDATA[We still experiencing some problems during the Ramacopters service chain. We should really invest some time to get even better! Let's service some Ramacopters from our Buddies.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.49.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Make your zoo smell nice Looks like we finally can service Ramacopters perfectly. Thats real good news, especially looking foward to the holiday season.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.49.ReturnPlane.2.name"><![CDATA[Return {number} Ramacopter-Quickie]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.50.name"><![CDATA[Support Your Shops]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.50.hint"><![CDATA[There are rumours that the shops manager is unhappy about the amount of cargo collected and resold to passengers. Let's try to improve her mood.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.50.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Well done! The shop manager seems to be very happy now! We should keep an eye on stocking up enough products in the future.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.50.SellProducts.name"><![CDATA[Sell {number} product(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.50.SendPlane.27.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-M-Cargo]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.51.name"><![CDATA[Announce Skyrama's Award]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.51.hint"><![CDATA[Hey, Skyrama want to recognise your performance by awarding you with an official sign - the ultimate stamp of approval! You should spread the word with your Buddies, both old and new.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.51.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Fantastic! Take a look into your storage to find the official sign from Skyrama. For sure, it will become a magnet for passengers!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.51.SendPlane.34.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} flyby(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.51.SendPlane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.52.name"><![CDATA[Help Your Cargo Buddies]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.52.hint"><![CDATA[Selling products is unsustainable unless you cooperate with your Buddies by sending them cargo too. Try and establish good cargo relations - service cargo planes sent by your Buddies]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.52.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Great job, we are earning a lot of AirCoins by selling the products. As a reward your warehouse-capacity has been upgraded.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.52.ReturnPlane.27.name"><![CDATA[Return {number} Rama-M-Cargo]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.52.ReturnPlane.20.name"><![CDATA[Return {number} Rama-XS-Cargo]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.52.ReturnPlane.28.name"><![CDATA[Return {number} Rama-M-Super Cargo]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.53.name"><![CDATA[Increase Your Ramacopter Traffic]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.53.hint"><![CDATA[We should give Ramacopters a higher profile. Make people think of us as a hub for Ramacopter routes - start sending and returning Ramacopters.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.53.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Superb! I would say people now consider us a highly-respected hub for Ramacopter flights.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.53.ReturnPlane.1.name"><![CDATA[Return {number} Ramacopter-Turbo]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.53.ReturnPlane.2.name"><![CDATA[Return {number} Ramacopter-Quickie]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.53.SendPlane.2.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Ramacopter-Quickie]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.53.SendPlane.3.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Ramacopter-Steady]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.54.name"><![CDATA[Reduce Your Noise Pollution]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.54.hint"><![CDATA[Groundstaff complain that the noise levels are intolerably high. We should build some sound barriers to protect their eardrums.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.54.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[That should be enough for now. The sound barriers will help improve groundstaff working conditions]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.54.ReturnPlane.3.name"><![CDATA[Return {number} Ramacopter-Steady]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.54.BuyLandsideBuilding.39.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} soundbarrier(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.54.GetAirCoins.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} AirCoin(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.55.name"><![CDATA[Explore Exciting Markets]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.55.hint"><![CDATA[There are some interesting countries with great business opportunities. Let's send some planes there. Go explore!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.55.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Good job! Tapping into new territories makes perfect business sense, and they are fun to visit too.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.55.SendPlane.42.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s) to Albania]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.55.SendPlane.47.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s) to Ukraine]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.55.SendPlane.56.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s) to Lithuania]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.55.SendPlane.38.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s) to Croatia]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.56.name"><![CDATA[Earn A Ramacopter-Seaking]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.56.hint"><![CDATA[We should think about restructuring the airport, buying some more decorations to increase the passengers rate, I have got a nice Ramacopter surprise for you when you are ready with those tasks. By the way, I think it's time to make some place for newer buildings, let's put the airhut into the storage.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.56.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Superb. The airport looks very pretty now! Take a look into your hangar - you will find the incredible wonderful fantastic Ramacopter-Seaking there! Seeeeend it!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.56.BuyLandsideBuilding.29.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} medium hotel(s) 2]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.56.BuyLandsideBuilding.47.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} water feature(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.56.StoreTerminal.1.name"><![CDATA[Place your old small Terminal in your storage]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.57.name"><![CDATA[Show-Off Your Ramacopter-Seaking]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.57.hint"><![CDATA[Aren't you proud of your brand new Ramacopter-Seaking? Send it to your Buddies! But take care to send some other aircraft, otherwise you'll look like a blatant show-off.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.57.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Well done! Everybody is wishing they had their own Ramacopter-Seaking.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.57.SendPlane.29.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-M-Super-Turbo]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.57.SendPlane.21.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-XS-Turbo]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.57.SendPlane.4.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Ramacopter-Seaking]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.58.name"><![CDATA[Keep Things Social]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.58.hint"><![CDATA[Your airport is humming along nicely but you should balance also business with pleasure. Go out of your way to keep things social.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.58.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Well done! You not only have a successful business but also good relations with your Buddies. It pays to be social.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.58.SendPlane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.58.SellProducts.name"><![CDATA[Sell {number} products]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.58.SendPlane.34.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} flyby(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.59.name"><![CDATA[Spread Your Traffic]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.59.hint"><![CDATA[We should impress our partners by establishing higher frequency medium plane routes between their airports and yours.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.59.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[That's what I call a business model! Income increased a lot thanks to you sending planes to our partners.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.59.SendPlane.2.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} medium plane(s) to Germany]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.59.SendPlane.33.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} medium plane(s) to Denmark]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.59.SendPlane.21.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} medium plane(s) to Russia]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.59.SendPlane.24.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} medium plane(s) to Portugal]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.60.name"><![CDATA[Provide More Taxis]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.60.hint"><![CDATA[The taxi manager told us that it's time to invest in a new taxi station if we want to get more passengers. Let's buy an airport taxi station!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.60.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[What a nice taxi station! Passengers seem to love it!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.60.BuyLandsideBuilding.56.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} airport taxi(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.60.SendPlane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.60.ReturnPlane.name"><![CDATA[Return {number} plane(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.88.name"><![CDATA[Seaplane Hangar]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.88.hint"><![CDATA[Island hopping is the new trend in adventure tourism. But many of those destinations don't even have a proper runway! We will need sea planes to take our customers there.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.88.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Excellent! We qualified for a new sea hangar. You can find it in your storage!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.88.BuyLandsideBuilding.73.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} Ticketshop]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.88.SendPlane.134.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to Brazil]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.88.GetPassengers.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} Passengers]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.88.ReturnPlane.127.name"><![CDATA[Return {number} planes from Mexico]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.88.SendPlane.plane.na.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to North America]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.88.SendPlane.helicopter.sa.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} helicopters to South America]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.89.name"><![CDATA[A crazy plan!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.89.hint"><![CDATA[Wow! Did you know that seaplanes are that expensive? I got us a deal with a big cargo company.  They agreed pay for our new sea port if we take care of some business for them.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.89.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Perfect! The cargo company was very pleased with our work! Find the new sea port in your storage.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.89.BuyPlane.11.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} SeaRama-Solo]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.89.GetAirCoins.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} AirCoins]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.89.SendPlane.27.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-M-Cargo]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.89.SendPlane.20.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-XS-Cargo]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.90.name"><![CDATA[First Seaplane]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.90.hint"><![CDATA[Now let's show off our new sea planes! That will show our customers that we are taking care of them.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.90.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[A job well done! That will attract even more passengers for the upcoming season.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.90.ReturnPlane.11.name"><![CDATA[Return {number} SeaRama-Solo]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.90.SendPlane.11.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} SeaRama-Solo]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.90.SendPlane.34.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} flybys]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.91.name"><![CDATA[Holidays]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.91.hint"><![CDATA[Its holiday time and that means a lot of business for our new seaplanes! Let's get those travelers to their destinations!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.91.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[We did it once again! Customers are happy and are sure to choose our airport again.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.91.SendPlane.85.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to Wyoming]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.91.SendPlane.124.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to South Carolina]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.91.SendPlane.102.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to Michigan]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.91.SendPlane.112.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to Connecticut]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.92.name"><![CDATA[Cargo Deal]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.92.hint"><![CDATA[Remember that cargo company that paid for our sea hangar? Well they just made us another offer we can't refuse. We should try to keep them happy to get more contracts in the future.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.92.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[And we succeeded again! The company is happy and will provide us with more jobs in the years to come.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.92.SendPlane.27.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-M-Cargo]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.92.SendPlane.20.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-XS-Cargo]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.92.ReturnPlane.20.name"><![CDATA[Return {number} Rama-XS-Cargo]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.92.ReturnPlane.27.name"><![CDATA[Return {number} Rama-M-Cargo]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.93.name"><![CDATA[Watertime]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.93.hint"><![CDATA[We have established our airport as one of the top seaplane hubs. Companies from all over the world trust in our expertise to handle their flights.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.93.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[We handled those seaplanes like real professionals! Now let's focus on our next tasks.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.93.SendPlane.12.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} SeaRama-Clipper]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.93.ReturnPlane.12.name"><![CDATA[Return {number} SeaRama-Clipper]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.93.SendPlane.11.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} SeaRama-Solo]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.93.SendPlane.34.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} flybys]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.94.name"><![CDATA[Helishow]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.94.hint"><![CDATA[Our PR department thinks that a helicopter show would help to get the attention of customers from the countryside. Those guys love big events like that! Let's get started.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.94.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Excellent! There was coverage of our show in all the local newspapers and television stations! Surely that will bring us some extra customers.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.94.SendPlane.3.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Ramacopter-Steadie]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.94.SendPlane.2.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Ramacopter-Quickie]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.94.SendPlane.4.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Ramacopter-Seaking]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.94.SendPlane.34.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} flybys]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.95.name"><![CDATA[Socialize]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.95.hint"><![CDATA[With all those new business opportunities we should not forget our old buddies! Let's strengthen the relationships to our friends by visiting them. But never forget to make new buddies as well.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.95.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Good work. Our old friends still remember us and some promising new relationships were established as well.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.95.GetPassengers.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} passengers]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.95.SendPlane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.95.SendPlane.34.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} flybys]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.96.name"><![CDATA[Holidays]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.96.hint"><![CDATA[We have to test out some new long distance routes. The goal is to find partner airports in each continent so we become part of an international network.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.96.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Success! We established some great long distance routes for the upcoming holiday season.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.96.SendPlane.14.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to Netherlands]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.96.SendPlane.25.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to Greece]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.96.SendPlane.130.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} medium planes to Dominican Republic]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.96.SendPlane.62.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} medium planes to Argentina]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.97.name"><![CDATA[Passengers]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.97.hint"><![CDATA[All those new planes and routes! We will need more passengers to keep the business running!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.97.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Great! That should do for the moment.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.97.SendPlane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} medium planes]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.97.SendPlane.34.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} flybys]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.97.GetPassengers.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} Passengers]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.97.BuyLandsideBuilding.71.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} car rental]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.98.name"><![CDATA[Action Day!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.98.hint"><![CDATA[Now we have the locations and the passengers so let's start sending our new fleet to all those great destinations!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.98.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Great our pilots love our new planes and our customers our new destinations! Keep up the good work.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.98.SendPlane.11.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} SeaRama-Solo]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.98.SendPlane.3.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Ramacopter-Steadie]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.98.SendPlane.4.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Ramacopter-Seaking]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.98.SendPlane.12.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} SeaRama-Clipper]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.99.name"><![CDATA[Cargo Challenge]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.99.hint"><![CDATA[Maybe we did a little too well on helping out that cargo company. Now requests from companies all over the world are coming in! Let's hope we can handle the upcoming challenge.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.99.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Success! The last cargo plane just hit the runway! As a reward we got a brand new warehouse-capacity upgrade!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.99.SendPlane.27.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-M-Cargo to Austria]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.99.SellProducts.name"><![CDATA[Sell {number} products]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.99.ReturnPlane.27.name"><![CDATA[Return {number} Rama-M-Cargo]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.99.SendPlane.27.sa.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-M-Cargo to South America]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.100.name"><![CDATA[Decorate]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.100.hint"><![CDATA[Fiona says we are focusing too little on the beauty aspect of live, and of course Tariq thinks she's absolutely right. So let's make them both happy by placing a viewing platform. That way visitors can admire all our beautiful decorations.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.100.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[I have to say Fiona was right. Some little decoration really can make a big difference.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.100.GetAirCoins.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} AirCoins]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.100.BuyLandsideBuilding.93.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} Viewing Platform]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.101.name"><![CDATA[Routinee]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.101.hint"><![CDATA[Safety is one of the most important issues of a modern airport. With all those new planes we should let our new pilots get some practice on our new aircrafts.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.101.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Perfect! Our pilots seem to handle the new aircrafts without a problem now.  Practice is important it seems.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.101.SendPlane.2.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Ramacopter-Quickies]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.101.SendPlane.11.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} SeaRama-Solo]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.101.SendPlane.helicopter.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} helicopters]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.101.SendPlane.seaplane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} seaplanes]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.101.SendPlane.plane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.102.name"><![CDATA[Socialize]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.102.hint"><![CDATA[Our airport is now one the finest worldwide when it comes to seaplanes. With that new status we should try to find some valuable partners that can keep up with us.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.102.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Many said it can't be done! But you managed to find some equally developed airports out there. It's always good to socialize in times like these.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.102.SendPlane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.102.SendPlane.134.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to Brazil]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.102.GetPassengers.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} Passengers]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.102.SendPlane.34.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} flybys]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.102.SendPlaneToStranger.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to a stranger]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.103.name"><![CDATA[Service Platform]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.103.hint"><![CDATA[Ok now our new partners want to test if we really are all that great. Let's show them that they can always count on us!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.103.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[All planes have been serviced in time! Saw their smiling faces? Surely they will choose our airport again.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.103.ReturnPlane.4.name"><![CDATA[Return {number} Ramacopter-Seakings]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.103.GetAirCoins.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} AirCoins]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.103.SendPlane.27.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-M-Cargo]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.103.SendPlane.20.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-XS-Cargo]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.103.ReturnPlane.seaplane.name"><![CDATA[Return {number} seaplanes]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.103.ReturnPlane.plane.name"><![CDATA[Return {number} planes]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.103.ReturnPlane.helicopter.name"><![CDATA[Return {number} helicopters]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.104.name"><![CDATA[The big Hotel]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.104.hint"><![CDATA[Only the biggest and best airports get the chance to crown themselves with a big hotel! So show the world our class and get that hotel built!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.104.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Great that hotel really makes the hole place special don't you think. I can't stop staring at it.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.104.GetAirCoins.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} Aircoins]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.104.BuyLandsideBuilding.76.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} Large Hotel]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.105.name"><![CDATA[Setup Your Tower]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.105.hint"><![CDATA[Time to begin adding some extra buildings to raise your airport's standards and put it on track for servicing bigger and better planes... Look in the store and get spending.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.105.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Well done! Your airport is starting to look very professional. In fact, the Airport Association says you are close to achieving standards required for servicing bigger planes.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.105.PlaceTerminal.2.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} medium tower(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.105.SendPlane.21.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-XS-Turbo]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.126.name"><![CDATA[Global village]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.126.hint"><![CDATA[The world is growing together! We need to establish international routes if we want to be a global player.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.126.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[That's the spirit! Our partner's around the world are happy to see that we are keeping up the good work!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.126.SendPlane.58.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s) to Canada]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.126.SendPlane.62.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s) to Argentina]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.127.name"><![CDATA[Business Class]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.127.hint"><![CDATA[More and more business men need flights to the financial centres of the world. Those are well paying clients that can bring us a lot of money.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.127.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Excellent! hose well paying customers could become the backbone of our airports economy!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.127.SendPlane.114.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s) to New York]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.127.SendPlane.79.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s) to California]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.127.SendPlane.138.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s) to Panama]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.127.SendPlane.61.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s) to Brasil]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.128.name"><![CDATA[Intercontinental Flights]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.128.hint"><![CDATA[Adventure Tourist are exploring destinations all over the world. We need to establish some routes to exotic places to keep customers happy!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.128.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Wonderful! Our airport is known for it's wide range of exotic destinations. Well done!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.128.SendPlane.63.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s) to Bolivia]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.128.SendPlane.133.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s) to Guatemala]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.128.SendPlane.140.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s) to Jamaica]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.128.SendPlane.107.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s) to Alaska]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.410.name"><![CDATA[Modernize It]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.410.hint"><![CDATA[In our business it’s essential to always be up to date. I heard about this brand new plane, the RamaWing-Eclipse. Adding it to our fleet will let people know we take modernization seriously.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.410.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Nice! That surely showed our competitors that we’re still an up to date airport.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.410.ReturnPlane.name"><![CDATA[Return {number} plane(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.410.BuyPlane.50.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} RamaLiner-Eclipse]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.410.SendPlane.50.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Ramaliner-Eclipse]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.411.name"><![CDATA[Safety Measures I]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.411.hint"><![CDATA[I talked to our analysts and they say it’s irresponsible to invest in expensive new buildings as long as we don’t even have the basic security buildings. I know what you’re thinking now: Analysts what do they know about running an airport! But they might be right about that one.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.411.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Excellent work! Our analysts are happy now. We fulfill all the preconditions to become a modern and safe airport.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.411.BuyLandsideBuilding.78.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} Firestation]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.411.GetPassengers.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} Passengers]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.411.SendPlane.helicopter.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Helicopters]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.412.name"><![CDATA[Power Up]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.412.hint"><![CDATA[If we want that fancy new terminal one day we will need a lot more energy than we currently have.  Also the state commission pays airports that use sustainable energy forms. So let’s build some new wind power plants and even get paid for it!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.412.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Excellent! We have enough energy now and our government paycheck also arrived. What a day!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.412.PlaceLandsideBuilding.86.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} Wind Power Plants]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.412.GetAirCoins.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} Air Coins]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.412.SendPlane.50.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Ramaliner-Eclipse]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.413.name"><![CDATA[Speed Up]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.413.hint"><![CDATA[With all that energy at our hands now we can reduce the service time of our bays. Place some of the tech-decorations next to your bays. That will motivate our packers and bring you a bonus on the service time of that bay.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.413.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Noticed how the service time of the bay went down when you placed those decorations next to it? A job well done!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.413.SendPlane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.413.PlaceLandsideBuilding.35.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} Cargo Pile]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.413.PlaceLandsideBuilding.33.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} Cone Set 1]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.414.name"><![CDATA[Bay Testing]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.414.hint"><![CDATA[Let’s test our new bays by sending and servicing some planes. That I don’t have to wait quite as long before takeoff is something I already love!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.414.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[See! Those new decorations really make a difference. If we plan wisely we can get a lot out of this!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.414.SendPlane.27.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-M-Cargo]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.414.SendPlane.seaplane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Seaplanes]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.414.SendPlane.helicopter.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Helicopters]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.414.SendPlane.plane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Standard Planes]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.415.name"><![CDATA[Safety Measures II]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.415.hint"><![CDATA[Ok so our buildings are protected from fire now. But what happens when a passenger gets sick? That’s nothing a water gun can fix. We need a First Aid Station to be prepared for everything.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.415.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Well done! Our analysts are happy now. We fulfill all the preconditions to become a modern and safe airport. As a little extra we got a brand new Ramaliner-Eclipse! Find it in your storage.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.415.BuyLandsideBuilding.110.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} First Aid Station]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.415.GetPassengers.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} Passengers]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.415.SendPlane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.416.name"><![CDATA[Cargo Cartel]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.416.hint"><![CDATA[The Cargo Cartel noticed our airports ambitions and offered to support our plans with a special surprise if we take care of some of their business. I’m not sure what the surprise will be but those big cargo companies always pay up.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.416.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[They are more than happy with us, but how could they not be! The surprise they had for us is a quick little cargo plane! Find it in your hangar.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.416.SellProducts.name"><![CDATA[Sell {number} Products]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.416.SendPlane.27.sa.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-M-Cargos to South America]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.416.SendPlane.27.eu.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-M-Cargos to Europe]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.424.name"><![CDATA[SWAP-A-JOB 1/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.424.hint"><![CDATA["What the heck is this 'Swap a Job' hog swallop about? If I’da wanted to be a dat-burned air traffic controller, then I woulda darn well been an air traffic controller! Whose genius idear was this anyway? You reckon it’s gone work out to have a flight attendant flyin’ the dang plane? I suppose I don’t have a choice – now, where’s that blasted rabbit’s foot o’ mine? Here it is. Now, can you help me return these flights without gettin' anybody hurt?"]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.424.rewardMsg"><![CDATA["Ooooh my gosh, I am like so totally proud of you, Kurt! You did an amazing job returning those flights. Not ONE plane crashed, either. Seriously, soooo awesome! Don't be silly - it was totally my pleasure to help. And honestly, like, it almost sounds like you had fun up there. Not so bad, right? Who me? In the hangar?? Eeeeeew! Are you serious? It's totally grody in there! I'm working in the gift shop. It was soooo much fun and honestly kinda relaxing. I got to arrange all the stuff in the shop however I wanted to. I got to talk to people from all over the world AND they even let me keep this stuffed pig as a souvenir!"]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.424.SendPlane.na.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to North America]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.424.SendPlane.eu.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to Europe]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.424.SendPlane.sa.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to South America]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.425.name"><![CDATA[SWAP-A-JOB 2/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.425.hint"><![CDATA["I am like, so totally excited for Swap-a-Job!! Initially, I was supposed to swap jobs with Kurt but then I complained to because guh-ross! Work in that dark, nasty hangar and get like oil or grease or whatever all over my clothes?? Yeah, right! Anyway, can I ask you for, like, a small favor? Can you help Kurt sound out flights without crashing any planes. You are awesome! How'd I end up in the gift shop, you ask? I just begged to be put there until I got my way. But I had to promise to personally pick out gifts for everyone because, between you and me, I think everyone is totally pissed about Swap-a-Job."]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.425.rewardMsg"><![CDATA["Oh my gosh it was like soooooo totally awesome in the gift shop. I cannot WAIT to tell you about all the presents I got for everyone - you're gonna love 'em! For Lin, I picked out this very special handbag. For Kurt, I have a brand new screw driver. Tariq is getting a little black book, of course. And I got hiking boots for Cassandra. I don’t really know her, but it seems like she’d totally be into that kinda thing. Wasn't that, like, totally sweet of me? What's that? Do I think the souvenirs will cheer everyone up about Swap-a-Job? Ummmm, no, not really. But, like, who doesn't like getting presents?"]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.425.SendPlane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.425.SellProducts.name"><![CDATA[Sell {number} products]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.425.SendPlane.27.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-M-Cargos]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.417.name"><![CDATA[Scientific Support]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.417.hint"><![CDATA[The local university thinks our airport would be the perfect spot for their new wheater balloon.  They are willing to pay pretty well and this could bring us some business class scientist customers. Let’s do it!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.417.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Nicely done! The balloon is up and working. Our payment has arrived and we had the first visitors already.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.417.PlaceLandsideBuilding.112.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} Wheater Balloon]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.417.SendPlane.21.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-XS-Turbo]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.417.SendPlane.na.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to North America]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.418.name"><![CDATA[Fancy New Terminal]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.418.hint"><![CDATA[The crown jewel of every modern airport is a state of the art terminal. Modern terminals combine functionality and leisure. They are assembled of two fully functional bays for medium planes and a sweet little coffee shop on the roof. Let’s get one built!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.418.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[And there it is! Isn’t it a beauty! Congratulations on completing your airports modernization!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.418.GetPassengers.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} passengers]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.418.PlaceBay.10.name"><![CDATA[Place Modern Terminal 2]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.418.SendPlane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.433.name"><![CDATA[On cloud nine 1/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.433.hint"><![CDATA[It’s not easy being a heart-breaker, let me tell you. Even the smoothest ladies’ man would get confused with a girlfriend at every airport. I mean, you know how lucky I am with the ladies – that’s not the problem. But sometimes I wonder if there’s more to life – maybe there’s something wonderful I’m missing out on. I mean, I can‘t be playboy forever, can I? Maybe I should put away my little black book, find a nice woman and settle down for good. She’s gotta be out there somewhere.
Come on – let’s start looking!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.433.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Good news! She’s the one – she’s the woman of my dreams. You know Lin, right? Well, I just saw her in the hallway and she smiled and said, “Hello, Tariq,” in this really seductive, sultry voice. If that’s not a clear sign she’s in love with me, I don’t know what is. Who could blame her? She is only human, after all. What should I do? What should I say? You have to help me – I cannot afford to screw this up!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.433.SendPlane.plane.51.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to Sweden]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.433.SendPlane.plane.149.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to New Zealand]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.433.SendPlane.plane.47.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s) to Ukraine]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.433.SendPlane.plane.137.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to Costa Rica]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.434.name"><![CDATA[On cloud nine 2/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.434.hint"><![CDATA[This is Operation Woo and Awww, soldier. The objective is clear and simple – we shower Lin with presents and compliments until she is disoriented. Then we give her more flowers, whisper even more sweet nothings in her ear. She’ll grow weak in the knees and that’s when we – and by we I mean, I – go in for the kill. Got it? Excellent – you know what to do, soldier!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.434.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Hello there, pookie! Long time no see – feels like it’s been weeks, months even! Well, now that you’re here, I’ve got something to tell you, but before I tell you, you have to promise to lock this secret up and throw away the key! I’ve met someone! Squeeeeee! What’s he like? Well, he’s a pilot. He’s soooooo cute. More than cute, really – he is built like an absolute Adonis. He makes my little heart go pitter-pat! Take the other day, for instance: he smiled at me in the hallway and, for the next two hours, it felt like I was walking on air! I hope he calls soon …]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.434.CollectSouvenir.12.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} gift(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.434.CollectSouvenir.14.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} candy/candies]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.434.CollectSouvenir.15.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} flower(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.435.name"><![CDATA[On cloud nine 3/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.435.hint"><![CDATA[OMG, I am freaking out! Look at my hands – they are totally shaking! I got a visit from the UPS man this morning and he unloaded what seemed like half of his truck on my doorstep. Every single package is a present. For ME! From my secret admirer!! Can you believe it?? This has never happened to me before. Oh my goodness, how sweet, right? He’s too shy to even approach me. That’s ok, though – I am pretty sure I know who my generous gentleman suitor is. The handsome pilot, of course! Ah! This is so exciting! I can’t wait 'til work’s over – I can’t focus on anything else.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.435.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[The presents have already been delivered. The rest of Operation Woo and Aww should be a walk in the park - All she has to do is unwrap the gifts. She’ll feel excited, maybe a little confused. Delirious, even. Then I swoop in and impress her with my world-class wit and irresistible charms. It’s basically a done deal. You know, I saw her in the food court the other day and she avoided making eye contact with me. That’s how nervous I make her! I’m telling you, the chemistry between us is electric. She’s just playing a little hard to get. That’s ok – she must know how much I love that!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.435.GetPassengers.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} passenger(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.435.ReturnPlane.name"><![CDATA[Return {number} flight(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.435.SendPlane.17.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-Xplore]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.436.name"><![CDATA[On cloud nine 4/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.436.hint"><![CDATA[Hi there, pumpkin! Things are getting really serious. I did everything I could to pump the UPS man for information. I was relentless – I kinda startled myself, honestly. I didn’t ease up until he handed over my honey-bunny’s address. You know the weirdest part? He and this total creep I work with live in the same building. Oh god, you don’t think they live together, do you? I hope not – this particular co-worker makes my skin crawl. I’d hate to have to see him outside of work, too.

I’ve had enough of this cat and mouse game. I’m going all in! As soon as I’ve set aside enough money, I’m gonna buy my secret lover a gorgeous golden pocket watch. AND I’m going to hand deliver it!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.436.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Dude, dude, dude! Come here, quick! I gotta tell you something. The UPS man just told me that Lin has been hounding him like a harpy for her secret admirer’s address. He finally gave in and sang like a canary, which is technically a felony, but I have bigger things to worry about. Like the fact that Lin is probably on her way here now! Crap, what am I doing standing around talking to you?! I gotta get myself cleaned up!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.436.SellProducts.name"><![CDATA[Sell {number} product(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.436.GetAirCoins.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} AirCoin(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.436.SendPlane.27.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama M Cargo/s]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.437.name"><![CDATA[On cloud nine 5/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.437.hint"><![CDATA[Hey there, cutie pie. Guess who’s got a new boyfriend? Just guess! ME! I was about to leave to visit my knight in shining armor, when all of sudden I saw him sitting in a tree in the parking lot. A little weird, I know, but he’s into watching butterflies – which is kind of perfect, since just thinking of him gives me butterflies! Heehee! His name is Axel, he’s a junior pilot and he’s sooooo cute. Seriously. So cute! Oh and get this – he totally does not live in Tariq’s building. Can you believe that? I bet the UPS man was just trying to get me off his back. Thank goodness I didn’t go over there! That would have been awkward.
Sigh, life is a dream, don’t you think? Well, ta-ta for now. Axel is taking me shopping. Siiiigggghhh! I’m so happy I feel like I might burst.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.437.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Ok, so – Lin didn’t show up yesterday after all because, apparently, she’s got a new boyfriend. Awesome, right? No, seriously – I am sincerely happy for her. So her new guy is a cue ball, big deal, right? And maybe he could learn a thing or two about personal hygiene, but who am I to judge? Axel will probably never be an impressive raconteur, but whatever makes Lin happy. That the only thing that matters.
Don’t worry about me – really! I’m ok. Honestly, I am very happy for the both of them. Now, if you’ll excuse me, I’d like to be alone. I’ve got a hot date with a buncha Twinkies. No! I’m not crying! There’s something in my eyes, ok? Just, go please.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.437.SendPlane.plane.114.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s) to New York]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.437.CollectSouvenir.7.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} handbag(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.437.CollectSouvenir.16.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} perfume(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.437.PlaceLandsideBuilding.111.name"><![CDATA[Place {number} cherry trees]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.438.name"><![CDATA[SWAP-A-JOB 1/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.438.hint"><![CDATA["What the heck is this 'Swap a Job' hog swallop about? If I’da wanted to be a dat-burned air traffic controller, then I woulda darn well been an air traffic controller! Whose genius idear was this anyway? You reckon it’s gone work out to have a flight attendant flyin’ the dang plane? I suppose I don’t have a choice – now, where’s that blasted rabbit’s foot o’ mine? Here it is. Now, can you help me return these flights without gettin' anybody hurt?"]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.438.rewardMsg"><![CDATA["Ooooh my gosh, I am like so totally proud of you, Kurt! You did an amazing job returning those flights. Not ONE plane crashed, either. Seriously, soooo awesome! Don't be silly - it was totally my pleasure to help. And honestly, like, it almost sounds like you had fun up there. Not so bad, right? Who me? In the hangar?? Eeeeeew! Are you serious? It's totally grody in there! I'm working in the gift shop. It was soooo much fun and honestly kinda relaxing. I got to arrange all the stuff in the shop however I wanted to. I got to talk to people from all over the world AND they even let me keep this stuffed pig as a souvenir!"]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.438.SendPlane.plane.af.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to Africa]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.438.SendPlane.helicopter.eu.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} helicopters to Europe]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.438.SendPlane.seaplane.au.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} seaplanes to Australia]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.439.name"><![CDATA[SWAP-A-JOB 2/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.439.hint"><![CDATA["I am like, so totally excited for Swap-a-Job!! Initially, I was supposed to swap jobs with Kurt but then I complained to because guh-ross! Work in that dark, nasty hangar and get like oil or grease or whatever all over my clothes?? Yeah, right! Anyway, can I ask you for, like, a small favor? Can you help Kurt sound out flights without crashing any planes. You are awesome! How'd I end up in the gift shop, you ask? I just begged to be put there until I got my way. But I had to promise to personally pick out gifts for everyone because, between you and me, I think everyone is totally pissed about Swap-a-Job."]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.439.rewardMsg"><![CDATA["Oh my gosh it was like soooooo totally awesome in the gift shop. I cannot WAIT to tell you about all the presents I got for everyone - you're gonna love 'em! For Lin, I picked out this very special handbag. For Kurt, I have a brand new screw driver. Tariq is getting a little black book, of course. And I got hiking boots for Cassandra. I don’t really know her, but it seems like she’d totally be into that kinda thing. Wasn't that, like, totally sweet of me? What's that? Do I think the souvenirs will cheer everyone up about Swap-a-Job? Ummmm, no, not really. But, like, who doesn't like getting presents?"]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.439.SendPlane.1057.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Ramaliner-M]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.439.SendPlane.29.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama M Super Turbo]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.439.SendPlane.40.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-Xperience]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.439.SendPlane.1065.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama S Quatro]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.440.name"><![CDATA[SWAP-A-JOB 3/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.440.hint"><![CDATA[*click*"Teehee, hey you guys! This is your Captain, Lin speaking. Heeheeheehee! Sorry, I am just tickled pink to be taking you to your final destination today." 
Calm down, Lin. Calm down. Ok, fine - get it out of your system: YIIIIIPPPPPPPEEEEE! Ok, for realsies this time: calm down! 
*click * "Tariq will be your seeing to your needs for the duration of this flight, so please don't hesitate to flag him down if you have any questions whatsoever. Hehehe, ahem. Sorry! For your inflight meal, you'll have a choice between rosemary roasted chicken with new potatoes - oh, yummy! That's what I would get - or farfalle pasta prima vera with parmesan. Oh! The tower just told me we're up next on the runway for takeoff, you guys! 
OH MY GOSH, Lin! This is really happening and I’m so excited – oh my goodness. What are all these buttons and knobs for?! 
*click* Paging Tariq to the cockpit! Ok, you guys. Heeeheee, prepare for takeoff!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.440.rewardMsg"><![CDATA["Tariq, I don't even know where to begin. You totally saved me - and everyone else on this airplane, for that matter. The tower cleared me for takeoff and it hit me that I was going to be flying a REAL plane. I took one look at all those knobs, buttons and flashing lights and I drew a blank. And then I panicked! I don't know what made me think I could successfully fly and land a plane after having completed a two-hour flight simulator! How can I ever repay you?"]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.440.SendPlane.plane.61.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to Brazil]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.440.SendPlane.plane.62.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s) to Argentina]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.440.SendPlane.plane.68.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Flugzeug/e nach Peru]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.441.name"><![CDATA[SWAP-A-JOB 4/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.441.hint"><![CDATA[You have GOT to be kidding me!! I cannot BELIEVE they are making me be a flight attendant. I'm the best pilot this airport has ever seen! I flown all around the world so many times I've lost count that I could land one of these jets in my sleep! I've never been so insulted  - what’s that? The contestants of the Caribbean Tropic bikini contest will be flying with us today? Hehe, n-n-no problem! I will do everything I can to make sure they have a pleasant flight! I’ll show them to their seats, help them store their luggage. Heck, I’d even help them apply their sun tan lotion! How does this sound: Would you like anything to drink, ma’am? Coffee, tea or me? Haha! Just a little flight attendant humor! 
Pull yourself together, Tariq. You've got this in the bag, buddy - all you have to do is make sure they have everything they need. How hard can it be, anyway? Just in case, can I count on you to help me keep the passengers content?]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.441.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[ME?! FIRED? How dare them – they simply can’t do this! I did everything I could to keep those women happy. They were so whiny - no, high maintenance. That's right! Those ladies were downright high maintenance. How was I supposed to keep them happy when they took issue with everything. It is completely their fault that I lost my job. I’ll never look at a woman in a bikini again the same way again. Oh MAN! Now I’m even MORE depressed.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.441.CollectSouvenir.6.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} lipstick(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.441.CollectSouvenir.35.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} Bikinis]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.441.CollectSouvenir.8.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} Jewels]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.442.name"><![CDATA[SWAP-A-JOB 5/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.442.hint"><![CDATA[I know I’ve been MIA lately, but to totally leave me out of the airport-wide Swap-a-Job event is just downright insulting. So I haven’t been around much lately, SUE ME. I've been doing my work, upholding my end of the bargain. All I've ever asked is that I be treated as an equal and now, THIS?! I am just so hurt - that's it! If they can't remember to include me, then they surely won't miss me if I hop in my sea plane and spend a couple weeks basking in the glorious Caribbean sun. Wanna come with?]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.442.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Aaaah, now THIS is the life! I don't think I've ever felt this relaxed – and tan! – in my entire life. I suppose I should head back to the airport. You know, as crazy as it sounds, I actually kinda missed it. The airport that is - they may be self-absorbed jerks, but they're MY self-absorbed jerks. Besides, now that I've had a couple weeks to cool off in the sweet, tropical shade, I am curious to know how Swap-a-Job went for everybody.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.442.SendPlane.seaplane.128.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} seaplanes to the Bahamas]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.442.SendPlane.seaplane.76.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} seaplanes to Hawaii]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.442.GetPassengers.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} passenger(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.world.1.name"><![CDATA[Trip around the world]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.world.1.ContinentUnlock.name"><![CDATA[Discovered continents]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.world.1.hint"><![CDATA[Explore every continent by visiting every country on a certain continent and grab exclusive items and a crimson red cargo plane for your globetrotting ways!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.world.1.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[A cargo plane for world travelers - With the Rama Global Cargo, the whole world is within reach. Import, export ... airport!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.443.name"><![CDATA[High Spirits 1/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.443.hint"><![CDATA[Hey, boss! Have you seen or heard anything, like, weird around here? Like around closing time? Define weird, you say? Umm, well like nothing super crazy. Just, you know, shadows that are blacker than black, demonic cackling, and OH MY GOD WHAT WAS THAT?! Did you see that? Oh god, we’re all doomed! <br><br>Ahem, sorry about that, sir. I didn’t mean to freak out like that. I just got a little spooked. Listen, something totally weird is going on around here. Like, Ghostbusters weird. It’s all over the airport by now. Around midnight is when strange stuff happens: people have heard tortured whimpers all over the terminal; luggage has disappeared into thin air; the smoothie machines don’t really work anymore. I mean, I never really believed in that hocus-pocus stuff but, like, I don’t know what to think now. What if we like crafted a bunch of food and put it out all over the place as, like, bait? Just to see what happens …]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.443.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Howdy! Whatever’s goin‘ on ‚round here stanks to high heaven. Last night, I was fixin’ ta load up a buncha traps with some mighty tasty lookin’ grub fer Fiona, when I heard this scream that was downright bloodcurdling’. Between you and me – I nearabout wet my britches, yessir. Next thing I knew, someone or something clobbered me on the backa the noggin’ and I passed clean out! Just came to ‘bout five minutes ago. I swaney, thangs just ain’t right round these parts.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.443.GetCargo.2.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} steaks]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.443.GetCargo.9.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} eggs]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.443.GetCargo.1.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} flour]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.443.SellProducts.name"><![CDATA[Sell {number} product(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.444.name"><![CDATA[High Spirits 2/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.444.hint"><![CDATA[Hi there! You know my boyfriend Axel, don’t you? He’s the beefcake over there with the gleaming smile. Anyway, he and his co-pilot Linda have been clocking lots of overtime lately and he says he feels like he’s being watched. Sounds paranoid, right? That’s what I said, but he swears it and I can’t convince him otherwise. Just the other day, he said a wailing banshee rushed him as he was boarding the plane. I told him how crazy he sounds, but he promises this shadow figure laughed and cursed at him. I told him he’s been working too much and needs some rest. Be a doll and plan a little vacation for him, would you?]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.444.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[You are a lifesaver! Thank you so much for your help. You planned quite the romantic get-away, but unfortunately I couldn’t go. Axel changed my flight plan at the last minute and sent me on a trip to Timbuktu! Thankfully, his co-pilot Linda was free so the ticket didn’t go to waste. Isn’t she a sweetheart? <br><br>Oh, listen to this! When I got back, there wasn’t a single, solitary soul at the entire airport! And then, when I was wandering through the terminal, I heard this faint moaning in the distance. It was sad, pathetic almost. Ulg! Just thinking about it gives me goose bumps. Whether I imagined it or not, it was totally spooky!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.444.SendPlane.25.name"><![CDATA[Start {number} Rama-M-Turbo to Florida]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.444.SendPlane.plane.178.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to Thailand]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.444.SendPlane.plane.au.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} medium planes to Australia]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.445.name"><![CDATA[High Spirits 3/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.445.hint"><![CDATA[Ga day, mate! Ya know what? I wish everyone’d just belt up about these ghost stories. Bloody oath, they are annoying! Just the other arvo I was comin‘ back from a 2 day pahty and all I could hear was buncha boofheads screamin’ “The ghost! There’s the ghost right there!” But THIS Sheiler ain’t afraida no styupid ghosts – know why? Cause I ain’t scared things that aren’t real! If I’ve said it once, I’ve said it a thousand toims, guests are the worst. We should round ‘em all and get the bush telegraph on who’s been muckin’ about the airport.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.445.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Hi there, hon! Have you seen Cassandra around lately? No one’s seen her since she started interrogating passengers. OH NO! You don’t suppose the ghost kidnapped her, do you?! Whatever happened to her, I hope she’s ok!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.445.GetPassengers.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} passenger(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.445.GetAirCoins.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} AirCoin(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.445.CollectSouvenir.50.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} Flashlights]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.446.name"><![CDATA[High Spirits 4/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.446.hint"><![CDATA[How yoouu? You know that gal Cassie, dontcha? Looks like she got hit by the ugly stick one too many times? Built like an outhouse? Anyway, the darndest thing – ain’t nobody laid eyes on ‘er since she started axin’ the passengers a buncha questions. Ever’body reckons she been abducted by that haint that’s been wreakin’ havoc ‘round here, but I gotta diff’rnt theory. Let’s start snoopin’ around those seaplanes and I’ll bet we find her.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.446.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Holy-dooly, mate – I feel like I got the wog! My head’s poundin’ like the surf! Thank goodness Kurt came nosin’ around my seaplanes – otherwise, I don’t think anyone woulda found me. I was so excited after the interrogations I wanted to celebrate. I was down the boozers with me cobber Dana, skullin’ one brownie after the other and, well, what can I say? I got a little carried away. What ya gonna do? <br><br>Oh, I almost forgot – one of the bloody passengers told somethin’ very interesting and now I’m pretty sure I know how we can catch this “ghost.” Just need a little toim.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.446.SendPlane.seaplane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Seaplanes]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.446.ReturnPlane.seaplane.name"><![CDATA[Return {number} Seaplanes]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.446.SendPlane.12.seaplane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} SeaRama-Clipper]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.447.name"><![CDATA[High Spirits 5/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.447.hint"><![CDATA[Okay, check this out. Eyewitness reports verify that the phantom appears when expensive planes and pretty women are in the vicinity. I say we get real clevah and set a trap. You get the fancy jet and I’ll convince Lin to help us out and Bob’s yer uncle, mate. Trust me, she’ll help – she’s doin’ her block cause her boyfriend’s been a real drongo.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.447.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Huh? Wh-what’s going on here? What happened? All I remember is that those corporate pigs laid me off and then I lost my apartment. But I still had my key to the airport so I decided to stay here. *sniff* I haven’t been doin’ so hot lately. First Lin dumped me *sniff* then I lost my job – it’s been too much to handle! I wanted to stay outta the way, so I crawled into the ventilation ducts and hunkered day to wait out the winter. I’ve been eating almost solely out of the snack machines and weeping. I tried to keep it down? <br><br>A ghost at the airport? Hmmm, that I don’t know anything about. Honestly, if there were a ghost at the airport, I would know about it. Hey, why are you looking at me like that? Why are you shaking your head? You don’t think people have confused ME for the ghost, do you? No way! <br><br>Oh, one more thing - *sniff* can I please have my job back? Plllllleeeeaaaaase?!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.447.SendPlane.40.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-Xperience]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.447.PlaceLandsideBuilding.93.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} Viewing Platform]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.447.CollectSouvenir.8.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} Jewels]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.447.GetAirCoins.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} AirCoin(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.448.name"><![CDATA[The Thin Line Between Love and Hate 1/4]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.448.hint"><![CDATA[I've searched for The One from one end of the planet to the other, but I'm still single. I just don't know what I'm doing wrong - or rather, what's wrong with women. How can they not see what an absolute catch I am?! It's SO obvious! That's it – I give up on love. Wait a minute – who is that ravishing creature over there? She is breath-taking! I must talk to her! I want to know everything about her – Oh and I have a flight to Toronto in like twenty minutes - can you start the flight for me while I see if I can get her to come along? Thanks!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.448.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[I think I'm falling in love! I never thought I'd meet a woman clever enough to realize how incredible am! I feel so lucky to have found her – she looks so good on my arm. That’s not the only reason, of course, but it doesn’t hurt. We’re so lucky to have found each other and to be travelling the world together. I won't reveal where I’m taking her next, but I’ll make sure we have good walking shoes and industrial-strength bug spray. You think you can help start the flight again?]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.448.SendPlane.1057.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Ramaliner-M to Canada]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.448.SendPlane.plane.na.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to North America]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.448.ReturnPlane.127.name"><![CDATA[Return {number} planes from Mexico]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.449.name"><![CDATA[The Thin Line Between Love and Hate 2/4]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.449.hint"><![CDATA[Can you start the flight to South American for us? I can’t wait to take Tara to the Amazon! It’ll be so romantic under the lush, exotic canopy of trees. There’s nothing quite like the rush of being surrounded by the wild, unadulterated outdoors. I mean ANYTHING could happen to us out there – we could be attacked by a wild animal at a moment's notice. We won't be attacked, of course, because I'll keep us safe, but still – it’ll be a thrill. I can’t wait!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.449.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[God, men are so stupid sometimes. He brought me to this overgrown, disease-infested hole? Do I look like the outdoorsy type to you? I tried to like it for his sake, but this place is too disgusting. I hope we're leaving for our next destination soon - I can't WAIT to get outta here. I wonder where he’s taking me next. It better be good this time! The City of Lights? Uhhh, I have no idea. OH! Paris! AWESOME! Ohmygoodness! I've never been to Paris before. I've heard the shopping is amazing.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.449.SendPlane.plane.61.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to Brazil]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.449.SendPlane.helicopter.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} helicopters to South America]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.449.CollectSouvenir.38.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} hairdryers]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.449.CollectSouvenir.36.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} Flip Flops]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.450.name"><![CDATA[The Thin Line Between Love and Hate 3/4]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.450.hint"><![CDATA[Be a friend and fly me and my special lady friend to Paris, will ya? I've got some romancing to do. Time to turn up the charm and try out my best French accent. How does this sound?
"Ooh la la, you will find zhis place is verry romantique. It has zhat certain je ne sais quoi - n'est-ce pas, mon cherie?” 
Pretty good, right? I hope it’ll be enough to keep her distracted – I don’t want her flirting with all of those sexy Parisian men. I suppose there’s no harm in flirting, just so she keeps it casual. After all, I am all the man she needs.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.450.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[My God! The lines at that, what's it called? Loo-vray? However you say it, the lines were insane. You can't really blame people, though. Did you see that piece of work by the exit?? Exquisite! A vision! It was worth standing around looking at a buncha globs of paint. No, no, not the Mona Lisa. I mean that security guard - hubba hubba! What a dream boat!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.450.SendPlane.plane.13.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s) to France]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.450.CollectSouvenir.3.name"><![CDATA[Collect  {number} french cheese/s]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.450.CollectSouvenir.32.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} coffee mugs]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.451.name"><![CDATA[The Thin Line Between Love and Hate 4/4]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.451.hint"><![CDATA[If I hope to turn this romance around, I’ll need your help! Send us to Australia on one last trip. Maybe the change in scenery will be all we need. Sydney should be the perfect place, don’t you think? It’s a beautiful, international hub of culture and entertainment! I could take her to the world-famous Sydney Opera House, the Royal Botanical Gardens and the beach. I was thinking we could take some surfing lessons. I also have some really lovely restaurants in mind – doesn’t that sound amazing? You’d like to go on a romantic getaway like this, wouldn’t you? Come again? Don’t forget to take her shopping? ULG, I suppose you have a point!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.451.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[I can’t believe her! Did she have to be so obvious about flirting with the surfing instructor?! No I will not calm down! Harmless flirting? HARMLESS?! She told him I was her Great Uncle!! How is that harmless?! You know something, she is without a doubt the most self-centered, egotistical person I’ve ever met! I can’t stand her and I never want to see her again. Please do me a favor, and fly this piece of work home. As for me, I’m going to go find about a pound of chocolate to ease my pain.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.451.SendPlane.seaplane.au.name"><![CDATA[Send  {number} seaplanes to Australia]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.451.SendPlane.helicopter.au.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} helicopters to Australia]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.451.SendPlane.au.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} medium planes to Australia]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.451.GetAirCoins.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} AirCoins]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.452.name"><![CDATA[Fever Pitch 1/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.452.hint"><![CDATA[I absolutely love this time of year – The International Airport Female Rugby finals are just around the corner! To secure the title, I’ve invited me cobbers from the team I was in at Uni and today’s the day to pick ‘em up. Can you help by heading down under? Cheers, mate!  I haven’t seen them in yonks, but I doubt anything’s changed – a bunch of yobbos, they are. I love ‘em, just the same. Besides, with my mates in my team, no one else will have a chance at the title!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.452.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[G’day, mates! The Sheilas are in town and are already lookin’ to get spiffed! I knew they’d be excited to be here, but I didn’t think they’d be THIS excited! I’ll have to keep a close eye on them so they don’t destroy the airport! In the meantime, I’d better get them a slab o’ tinnies or else they’re bound tear this place apart. This is definitely going to be interesting …]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.452.SendPlane.21.au.name"><![CDATA[Starte {number} Rama-XS-Turbo to Australia]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.452.PlaceLandsideBuilding.76.name"><![CDATA[Place {number} large hotels]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.452.GetCargo.2.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} steaks]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.452.GetAirCoins.name"/>
  <item name="av.goal.main.453.name"><![CDATA[Fever Pitch 2/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.453.hint"><![CDATA[This is bloody well like babysitting – except I’m not getting paid! The ladies are skulling amber fluid like it’s going outta style! They’re running amok all over the terminal – passing out in seats, in plants, bothering passengers waiting to board. I tell ya, I’ve not seen such behavior in a long time. You’d better send out as many flights as you can, so there’s no one here to pester!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.453.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Holy-dooly, mate! I can’t thank you enough for your help. You did a bang up job of getting the passengers out of the airport – these larrikins are holy terrors when they’ve had a bit of grog. I’ve gotta go! I have to make sure they’re not causing any more trouble. Keep in mind, I might need your help again.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.453.GetPassengers.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} passengers]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.453.CollectSouvenir.33.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} sunglasses]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.453.ReturnPlane.plane.name"><![CDATA[Send back {number} planes]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.453.GetAirCoins.name"/>
  <item name="av.goal.main.454.name"><![CDATA[Fever Pitch 3/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.454.hint"><![CDATA[I don’t believe it. I absolutely do not believe it. Now that most of the passengers are out of the terminal, my friends are annoying my fellow airport employees – this is totally not on, because I’m the one who will have to answer for them. Plus, everyone’s really excited about the rugby finals, so they don’t want to be rude to their team!  I need your help – return as many flights as you can so that the terminal’s full of people again and I’ll keep those rowdy Sheilas outta the way.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.454.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Crikey, you’re a lifesaver! *hearty pat on the shoulder* Onya! While you filled up the terminal with people, I took my bawdy cobbers to the hangar so they can’t bother anyone any more. Let’s just hope they don’t break anything! This better work, otherwise I’ll be too stuffed to play in the finals.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.454.SendPlane.plane.as.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} medium planes to Asia]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.454.SendPlane.100.eu.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Camo-Copters to Europe]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.454.SendPlane.plane.af.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to Africa]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.454.GetAirCoins.name"/>
  <item name="av.goal.main.455.name"><![CDATA[Fever Pitch 4/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.455.hint"><![CDATA[Just what in the hell do y’all thing yer doin’ in ma hangar! These ain’t toys, ya know – these planes ain’t here for yer amusement. The rugby team? Well shucks, ladies. I wisht you had told me that sooner. Now, y’all be careful climbin’ all over these airplanes, here? I’m the one who’ll hang if they get broke. Oh, and good luck at the finals tomorrow – speakin’ o’ the finals: where IS ever’body? How come more people ain’t already here? You better round up as many passengers as you kin, just to be sure.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.455.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[You are a god send, mate! I was so busy keepin’ my stroppy friends outta trouble that I totally forgot to gather passengers for the finals! You really saved my hide – I owe you a shout! Now to win the finals and get these birds back to the outback.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.455.GetPassengers.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} passengers]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.455.GetAirCoins.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} aircoin/s]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.455.CollectSouvenir.34.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} swim shorts]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.455.SellProducts.name"><![CDATA[Sell {number} products]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.456.name"><![CDATA[Fever Pitch 5/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.456.hint"><![CDATA[We won! It’s no surprise, really. My teammates may be a pain in the you-know-what, but they sure know how to play some rugby. Everyone at the airport is so proud, not to mention relieved they’ll soon be rid of their guests. Can you help me gather some things for the winners? We need some medi kits to mend our bumps and bruises, some cameras to take victory pics and some grapes and French cheese for their hard yakka. I promise they’ll nick off to Australia as soon as the party’s over!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.456.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Thank goodness that’s over! The ladies may be annoying, but they are bonzer mates. Not only that, but they said they had a blast. They thought everyone was really nice and they can’t wait to come back for the finals next year. What’s wrong? What’d I say, mate?]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.456.CollectSouvenir.48.name"><![CDATA[Coellect {number} medikits]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.456.CollectSouvenir.4.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} grapes]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.456.CollectSouvenir.3.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} french cheeses]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.456.CollectSouvenir.37.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} cameras]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.457.name"><![CDATA[You are NOT clear for landing … 1/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.457.hint"><![CDATA[Hi there! Ulg, Axel? What was I thinking? What kind of name is that anyway? What an insensitive JERK! You know he has a girlfriend at every airport?? What a miserable LIAR! I can’t believe I trusted him! All he thinks about is himself and could CARE LESS how I feel. What a PIG! I’ve never met a more despicable, low-down, dirty cheater in my entire life. I hope I never see him again. He can have back all his cheap presents – I can’t stomach looking at it for one more day. In return, I need you to send him on a trip around the world, while I arrange the perfect parting gifts for him. That lily-livered CHICKEN!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.457.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Ha! That sure showed HIM! I won’t be seeing that unfaithful pipsqueak again anytime soon. What a relief! And, hey – I’m single again! Sooo, awesome. I have time for myself again. I get to watch whatever I want on TV. I paint my nails every weekend, now that there’s no one to complain about the smell. I wear what suits me, style my hair however I want. I have the whole bed to myself again and I don’t have to pick up his stupid, dirty clothes off of the bathroom floor EVER AGAIN! I’m super pumped, Sweetpea. <br> <br>I just hope that the perfect pilot is still out there. No more mouth-breathing idiots in cheap suits for me. Nope, it’s Mr. Right or no one at all. What do you think, Muffin? Is the pilot of my dreams still out there, waiting for me to bring him in for landing on the runway of love?]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.457.SendPlane.plane.as.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to Asia]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.457.SendPlane.1067.af.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-M-Quatro to Africa]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.457.PlaceLandsideBuilding.52.name"><![CDATA[Place {number} Flying Cockerels]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.457.PlaceLandsideBuilding.50.name"><![CDATA[Place {number} cactus/cacti 2]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.458.name"><![CDATA[You are NOT clear for landing … 2/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.458.hint"><![CDATA[Hey, wingman! You heard the news? Lin’s back on the market! Thankfully, I am sooo over her – really, not bothered. I bent over backwards for her, rolled out the red carpet, but I’ll never make that mistake again. Never again will I be the lovesick puppy dog at her heels. Besides, I can have any woman I want – why go for someone else’s leftovers when I can have something fresh and piping hot? <br> <br>Anyway, I was doing some light reading last night and I saw that there are more women in China, India, the USA and Indonesia than any other countries in the world. I’m a little skeptical, so I thought we could fly there to do some research of our own. You interested?]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.458.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[I’ve good news and bad news – which do you want first? The bad news is that we’re no closer to disproving the claims in that book. The good news is that we have to do even more research all over the world! You should come along – I could really use your help. You know, I wonder if Lin would ever give me another chance – err, if I should give HER another chance, that is. On second thought, phooey on Lin! She ripped my heart outta my chest and danced flamenco all over it. Metaphorically, of course. Anyway, I’m all the company I’ll ever need.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.458.SendPlane.seaplane.186.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} seaplanes to China]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.458.SendPlane.helicopter.79.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} helicopters to California]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.458.SendPlane.plane.174.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} small planes to India]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.459.name"><![CDATA[You are NOT clear for landing … 3/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.459.hint"><![CDATA[Hi there, Puffin. Ulg, have you seen the new flight plan? They put me aboard Tariq’s flight. *Rolls eyes* I really can’t stand him! Why? You’ve obviously never met him, otherwise you wouldn’t have to ask. He’s a total disgusting pig, that’s why. He thinks he's god’s gift, but he’s really a pathetic loser. Luckily, I know how I’m gonna get out of it! Fiona’s in charge of the flight plan this week and I happen to know that she LOVES sweets. Cookies, pastries, cakes – you name, if it can give you diabetes, she loves it.  Gather all the sweets you can find and we’ll stuff Lin so fulla pastry that she’ll change the flight plan in a sugar-fueled frenzy.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.459.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Heyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyy! OMGOMGOMGOMG, I am suuuuuuper excited. Can’t explain now – too many places to go, too much to do. Gotta land all the planes, come hell or high water. Oh look, there’s hell. Hahahaha, just kidding. You get it? Anyway, heheh. Have you ever noticed what a totally weird word anyway is. Say it, anyway. Anywayanywayanywayanyway. See what I mean?! Super weird. Gosh, I have sooo much to do – I wanted to clean the entire tower and I still have to change this week’s flight plan. Got it – switch Axel and Tariq’s crews! Bada-bing. Hehehe, walk in the park. Man, I am like so dizzy. I think I’d better lay down …]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.459.GetCargo.1.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} flour]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.459.SellProducts.name"><![CDATA[Sell {number} goods]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.459.CollectSouvenir.14.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} candies]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.460.name"><![CDATA[You are NOT clear for landing … 4/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.460.hint"><![CDATA[Booooooo, are you serious?! Have you seen this week’s flight plan? They put Lin on my crew. Weak sauce! What, now she’s gonna make my life miserable just cause I turned her down? I mean really – grow up, Lin! Geez, women make me crazy! <br> <br>Ulg, I don’t wanna talk about women for the whole rest of the day. Besides, I’m pretty sure Cassandra can help us. She told me at a party last week that she knows where Fiona keeps the flight plans. All we gotta do is pick up a few souvenirs for Cassandra and she’ll do us a solid. I know it!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.460.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Oy, d’ya know Tariq’s been giving me all kindsa presents lately?! Yestahday he tried to get me to change the flight plan and I’m afraid he’s just tryin’ to weasel his way onto my crew. How many toims do I have to tell ‘im – I’m not into blokes. Like him, blokes like him. Ya know what I’m gonna do? I’m just gonna switch our floight plans – that way, I do him a favah and no one can say I’m an ingrate.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.460.CollectSouvenir.49.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} Lighters]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.460.CollectSouvenir.47.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} screwdrivers]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.460.CollectSouvenir.25.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} toothpaste]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.460.CollectSouvenir.1.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} tie(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.461.name"><![CDATA[You are NOT clear for landing … 5/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.461.hint"><![CDATA[What in the? Now Lin’s back in my crew! B-but – I thought Cassie was gonna help me out? She promised! I don’t understand! Even Lin was pretty ticked off. I just heard her screaming Fiona’s head off all over the airport. What a hot-head! Actually, I kinda like a lady with attitude. <br> <br>Oh, who am I kidding? I can’t stay mad at Lin forever – look at her. She’s so sweet and adorable. I just have to give her a second chance. Help me get her attention by writing love notes in the sky. She’s gonna love it!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.461.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[She must’ve seen my heartfelt love notes in the sky by now. She’s gonna love this. Should I change my clothes? Any minute now, she’s going to come find me, overcome with emotion<br> <br>Just a matter of minutes now. I can see her in my mind’s eye already – running towards me, like a scene from a romantic film. Ah, I can’t wait! <br> <br>Just gonna wait here patiently. I can’t be too much longer now. <br> <br>So, any second now, she’ll run towards me and I’ll catch her in my arms<br> <br>.I can’t wait. <br> <br>Oh, Lin. Come to, Tariq! <br> <br>Seriously, any day now!<br> <br>TO BE CONTINUED!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.461.SendPlane.34.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Flybys]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.461.ReturnPlane.helicopter.name"><![CDATA[Return {number} helicopters]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.461.SendPlane.helicopter.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} helicopters]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.461.GetAirCoins.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} aircoin/s]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.462.name"><![CDATA[There’s Something in the Air 1/3]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.462.hint"><![CDATA[G’day, mate! Have ya heard the rumors buzzin’ ‘round the airport? Apparently, there’s gonna be a big marriage proposal sometime this week. I think it’s pretty lame, but I’m also pretty sure no one’s about to ask for my hand. I wonder who it’s gonna be … I wonder if she’ll say yes? I’ll tell ya what I’d say – nick off, ya silly bugger! ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.462.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Rumors about a weddin’ proposal? Hell’s bells, I ain’t heard nothin’ about no weddin’ proposals ‘round here. I got work to do – you think I got time to stand around and flap my jaw with ever’body? These planes ain’t gonna fix themselves, ya know! Go talk Tariq – that old cad is probably the one who has the low down on this proposal business.  ]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.462.SendPlane.seaplane.186.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} seaplanes to China]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.462.SendPlane.helicopter.au.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} helicopters to Australia]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.462.ReturnPlane.name"><![CDATA[Return {number} flight(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.462.GetAirCoins.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} aircoin/s]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.463.name"><![CDATA[There’s Something In the Air 2/3]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.463.hint"><![CDATA[Pssh. Pop the question?! ME? Who would I propose to? And why would I do a thing like that? I couldn’t take myself off the market – it would crush all the hopeful bachelorettes out there. What would they have to strive for? Besides, you know Tariq likes to fly solo. Trust me, if I knew who was about to pop the question I’d be convincing him not to right now. ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.463.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Awwwwwww! Have you heard? Everyone’s talking about it! Someone is planning a big marriage proposal. It’s supposed to happen at some point this week, but no one knows when or where. Heck, no one even knows who’s proposing to whom. Some people think it’s cheesy but I think it’s suuuuper romantic … unless … you don’t think it’s Tariq, do you? Oh god, if he proposes to me, I’ll just die! What should I do? ]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.463.CollectSouvenir.23.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} windsock(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.463.SendPlane.plane.13.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s) to France]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.463.CollectSouvenir.38.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} hairdryers]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.463.SendPlane.plane.12.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} medium plane(s) to Spain]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.464.name"><![CDATA[There’s Something In the Air 3/3]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.464.hint"><![CDATA[OMG you guys, guess what? You know how everyone’s been talking about the marriage proposal. Well, I totally think it’s gonna happen like any minute now! The tower just got a request for 50 fly-bys – normally, we would never approve a request like that, but we figured it had something to do with the big question everyone’s been talking about all week. Don’t miss it! It’s gonna be totally awesome! ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.464.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Oh my gosh, I am like totally speechless. I have no idea what to say. Other than I never thought in a million years that Kurt was planning on proposing to me. And so publicly! It was like so completely beautiful and touching – we both got a little teary-eyed. We’re already starting to look at locations and dates and, OH, you have to come! I am super serious. It wouldn’t be the same without you. Can you believe it?! This is so exciting! ]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.464.SendPlane.34.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Flybys]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.464.CollectSouvenir.12.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} gift(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.464.SendPlane.helicopter.eu.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} helicopters to Europe]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.464.GetPassengers.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} passengers]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.465.name"><![CDATA[Bells Will Be Ringing 1/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.465.hint"><![CDATA[Oh my gosh! I'm soooooo excited. Hehe. Did I say excited? Hehe. I meant to say stressed. Taut like a string about to snap, is more like it. The wedding is just days away, as you know hehe, and Fiona and Kurt have asked us to pitch in. They don't think they'll pull it off in time, otherwise. Fiona says she thinks I have lots of style and that, if she can't do it all herself, she trusts no one more than me to organize the flowers, catering and music. Hehe. Sooo sweet! I feel so honored. Did I say honored? I meant I can't feel my eyeballs. That's normal, right? Hehe. Heh. HAAARGH! HELP ME, PLEASE!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.465.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Oh geez, have you seen Lin around anywhere? Gosh, I feel, like, super bad for keeping her so busy for our wedding, but like we all talked about it, and we think it's for the best. We think keeping her busy will keep her mind off the fact that she isn't the one getting married. I gotta make sure that she's like still eating and sleeping and stuff. I wouldn't want her to miss the bouquet toss!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.465.CollectSouvenir.3.name"><![CDATA[Collect  {number} french cheese/s]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.465.CollectSouvenir.4.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} grapes]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.465.BuyLandsideBuilding.44.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} flowerbox/flowerboxes]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.465.CollectSouvenir.22.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} coffeemachine(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.466.name"><![CDATA[Bells Will Be Ringing 2/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.466.hint"><![CDATA[G'day, ya gobbers! When Kurt and Fiona asked me to help them with their weddin', I originally told them to sod off, but when they explained they wanted me in chahge of drinks … well, I couldn't say NO, could I? They said no one knows how to pahty like I do and that they need the amber fluid to flow, make sure spirits run high, all that. I can't say that I blame them for asking for my help. Who better to see after the most important part of this special occasion, than a self-proclaimed professional pahty animal? I just need ya to lend me a hand with the libations, mate.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.466.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Fifi and I don't even really drink and we kinda hate encouragin' Cassandra's partyin' like this, but we really need a second pilot on board our weddin' flight, cause Tariq is a wild card. We're also not too sure how he feels about this whole thing, so better safe 'n sorry, as my Momma always said. We've put Lin on Operation Sober Up to make sure Cassandra doesn't get TOO, err, woozy and that we got plentya coffee brewed at all times. Now if you'll excuse me, Fifi and I gotta go get the rings and our weddin' license.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.466.CollectSouvenir.12.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} Gifts]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.466.ReturnPlane.plane.name"><![CDATA[Send back {number} planes]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.466.GetPassengers.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} passengers]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.467.name"><![CDATA[Bells Will Be Ringing 3/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.467.hint"><![CDATA[Yes, of course I'm happy for Kurt and Fiona! Why does everyone keep asking me that? I mean, I think any man who decides to get married is a fool, but who am I to stop Kurt from making the biggest mistake of his life? Between you and me, he actually seems pretty happy so, when they asked me to book the bishop, I gladly said yes. They insisted that I get to know some religious people. Fiona even said to me, “I hope you, like, find God or whatever.” Anyway, I know just the guy. I just need you to start a flight to Italy for me.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.467.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Like, I know it's kinda crazy to make Tariq responsible for booking the person who will marry Kurt and I, but I was not kidding – he needs religion! Anyway, we're hoping that if he books the bishop, he'll be more aware that there is a man of the cloth aboard the plane and behave accordingly. It's like a longshot or whatever, but we figured it couldn't hurt to try. Wait, what time is it? Crap! I gotta go – I'm late for my final dress fitting!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.467.SendPlane.plane.7.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to Italy]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.467.CollectSouvenir.48.name"><![CDATA[Coellect {number} medikits]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.467.GetPassengers.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} passengers]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.467.GetAirCoins.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} AirCoins]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.468.name"><![CDATA[Bells Will Be Ringing 4/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.468.hint"><![CDATA[What was I thinking? Why did I agree to service this wedding flight? Let me tell you, that Fiona can be convincing! She wouldn't take no for an answer. She kept insisting that their wedding wouldn't be the same without me there, but now I think she didn't have anyone else to do it. Can I count on your to help me service the flight? All you have to do are prepare snacks and drinks. I’m sure it’ll be fine anyway. I love weddings – or should I say free food and free drinks. Besides, making Tariq uncomfortable will be the icing on the cake!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.468.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[I was real uncomfortable with havin’ Tara servicing the flight, but Fifi assured me we didn't have any other choice. She's right: we really need her there. And if I'm bein' honest, I look forward to seein' Tariq squirm. Not too much longer, now. Before ya know it, I'll be watchin' my bride come down the aisle. I feel like the luckiest man at this whole crazy airport! Anyway, I gotta go – Fiona and I are goin' to order the cake!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.468.CollectSouvenir.18.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} Travel Pillows]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.468.CollectSouvenir.22.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} coffeemachine(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.468.CollectSouvenir.32.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} coffee mugs]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.468.SendPlane.plane.na.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to North America]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.469.name"><![CDATA[Bells Will Be Ringing 5/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.469.hint"><![CDATA[Clean the plane, they said! Make sure it's spotless top to bottom, nose to tail. I know how to clean a plane, you idiots! Typical! Let's have Tariq pick up our mess, because we didn't invite the cleaning lady?? Such a load of bull! Who's surprised, though? Buncha selfish jerks! Come on – I need your help getting this plane cleaned up. ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.469.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[I know it's like pretty messed up that we didn't invite the cleaning lady. But she's really grumpy and none of us really know her. We're nervous enough about our wedding party as it is – we don’t want to add a volatile, unpredictable element to the mix. We need nothing but clear skies and smooth sailing. Oh, gotta go! It's time to get into my dress! Heeheehee, I can't believe I'm getting MARRIED!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.469.SellProducts.name"><![CDATA[Sell {number} products]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.469.GetPassengers.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} passengers]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.469.ReturnPlane.plane.name"><![CDATA[Send back {number} planes]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.469.SendPlane.seaplane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Seaplanes]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.470.name"><![CDATA[Crashing the Bachelor Party 1/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.470.hint"><![CDATA[There’s no turning back now. Kurt’s getting married tomorrow, which is fine by me. He gets a new bride and I have less competition. He doesn’t know it yet, but tonight we’re taking him on the wildest bachelor party ever, planned by yours truly. This’ll be great: Kurt will have one last hoorah and I’ll get to pick up on hot chicks all night.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.470.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Hi there, puddin‘ cake! I don’t believe what I’m seeing … is the champagne not on ice yet?! Are you trying to give me a heart attack? Sorry, I may be a little on edge because of Kurt and Fiona’s wedding. I’ve been busy organizing the flowers, food, music AND bachelorette party. It’s ok, though: the bachelorette party’s going to be a hoot. I can’t wait to see those chiseled, exotic dancers on the Chippengales stage. All my hard work will have been worth it!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.470.CollectSouvenir.33.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} sunglasses]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.470.CollectSouvenir.51.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} Fire Extinguisher]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.470.CollectSouvenir.4.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} grapes]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.470.SendPlane.plane.12.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to Spain]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.471.name"><![CDATA[Crashing the Bachelor Party 2/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.471.hint"><![CDATA[Mornin! Tomorrow is the big day and I got about as many butterflies as I did at my third weddin. Or was it my fourth? Anyway, Fiona is a keeper and I’m tickled pink. I saw ma grandchildren earlier and they sure are excited. All I need is a good night’s sleep and I’ll be right as rine. Right as roam. Right as … ulg, I’m not feelin so hot. Why is the room spinnin‘? I’m seein‘ doub … zzzzz … zzzzz … zzzzz.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.471.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[See? One whiff of my dirty old gym socks and he’s out like a light! Now to get that him to the greatest bachelor party of all time. I have a Chippengales coupon from an ex-girlfriend that we’re gonna use tonight. Never heard of ‘em before, but it sounds like a good time. Kurt won’t know what hit him!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.471.CollectSouvenir.37.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} Cameras]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.471.SendPlane.plane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.471.SendPlane.seaplane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Seaplanes]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.472.name"><![CDATA[Crashing the Bachelor Party 3/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.472.hint"><![CDATA[I am so excited for my bachelorette party! Lin planned, like, everything. She’s brought us to a dance performance, but I can’t remember the company’s name. Whoever they are, they don’t wear much clothing. I think all this schnapps is starting to go to my head, because the guy in the audience looks like Kurt … that IS Kurt! WHY IS KURT HERE?! ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.472.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Zzzz … zzzz … Huh?!? Wh-where am I?! What’s goin on? Why is Tariq wavin money in front of my face? Why is my lil Fifi runnin at me with an empty champagne bottle in her hand? Why does she have murder in her eyes? Gracious, what have y’all done to my honeybun? Fiona, it’s ok … I’m fi … *CLANK*]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.472.PlaceLandsideBuilding.76.name"><![CDATA[Place {number} large hotels]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.472.SellProducts.name"><![CDATA[Sell {number} goods]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.472.SendPlane.helicopter.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} helicopters]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.473.name"><![CDATA[Crashing the Bachelor Party 4/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.473.hint"><![CDATA[Oh, man! Fiona wiped the dance floor with poor Kurt and then started screaming at me that this was all my fault. AS IF this was my fault! STOP SCREAMING, already. I may not look it, but I am a sensitive soul and *sniff* you’re hurting my feelings!<br><br>Can you take care of my work at the airport? I’ve got some cleaning up to do around here. <br><br>]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.473.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Mornin! That Tariq is a so-and-so, ain’t he? He knows how much Fiona loves bottles and, when he pulled one outta his bag, she fainted right there on the spot. Why does she love bottles so much? I haven’t the foggiest.<br><br> When she came to, we just told her it was all a dream. Now all I gotta do is tell her why I got this knot on my head.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.473.SendPlane.plane.na.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to North America]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.473.SendPlane.plane.sa.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to South America]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.473.SendPlane.plane.7.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to Italy]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.473.SendPlane.seaplane.au.name"><![CDATA[Send  {number} seaplanes to Australia]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.474.name"><![CDATA[Crashing the Bachelor Party 5/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.474.hint"><![CDATA[Hey! I just had the funniest dream. I dream that Tariq was swinging his hips and Lin was swinging her fists. Neon lights – there were neon lights everywhere. Everyone was yelling, “It wasn’t me! It’s not my fault!“ And then some awful woman came out of nowhere and beat up my sweet Kurt. I know what this all means: they’re all good omens for our marriage! Now that I’m feeling better, I’m gonna hold on to Kurt and never let him go!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.474.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Ok, ok – things could have gone a little smoother at the bachelor party. I had the best of intentions, believe me. Good intentions count just as much  - if not more than – a job well done. Besides, it wasn’t all terrible. The Chippengales offered me a beginner’s dance course!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.474.SellProducts.name"><![CDATA[Sell {number} products]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.474.SendPlane.34.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Flybys]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.474.SendPlane.plane.13.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s) to France]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.475.name"><![CDATA[Bells Will Be Ringing 1/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.475.hint"><![CDATA[Mornin! Today's the big day. The Bishop from Las Vegas should be here any minute to wed me and my sweet Fiona. Hurry, if we stand round here flappin our jaws all day, we'll miss the Just Married Discount at the hotel!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.475.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Hi there, sweetheart! I'm sooo glad you're here - I could use a hand organizing the food, music and flowers for this wedding. Can I go over the menu with you? I just want to make sure I have everything straight. For starters, we'll have finger cucumber sandwiches. Wait, that's not right. OH NOOOOO! <br><br>Calm down, Lin. You can do this. Focus - remember, all that matters is catching that bouquet.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.475.PlaceLandsideBuilding.9.name"><![CDATA[Place {number} Flower Circles]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.475.PlaceLandsideBuilding.85.name"><![CDATA[Place {number} bonsai]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.475.SendPlane.plane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.476.name"><![CDATA[Bells Will Be Ringing 2/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.476.hint"><![CDATA[A very good morning to you, young man. Young lady? Who can be sure these days. Allow me to introduce myself - I am Bishop Malcolm from Las Vegas and I'm here to wed a young couple in holy matrimony. But first, I think I'll try some of that tasty fish. <br><br>*Mmmmm*<br><br>Funny, I'm suddenly not feeling well. That safety video, it reminds me of my life. Just so fast and in reverse. <br><br>…<br><br>…<br><br>…*wheeze*…<br><br>Is there a doctor on board ...]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.476.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Hey, buddy! What's up? I was just on my way to the little pilot's room. Wha?! What is that? What's wrong with the Bishop? Who does he think he is? I'm usually the one with no manners. <br><br>Wait just a minute. His lips are turning blue. He's dead! What are we gonna do? The Bishop is dead!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.476.CollectSouvenir.48.name"><![CDATA[Coellect {number} medikits]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.476.SendPlane.plane.2.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to Germany]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.476.SendPlane.plane.7.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to Italy]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.477.name"><![CDATA[Bells Will Be Ringing 3/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.477.hint"><![CDATA[Hi! Have you heard people talking about this "nightmare wedding?" Apparently this couple wanted to get married in the air, but the Bishop who was supposed to married them died on board! Isn't that crazy? Wait a minute ...<br><br>that's ... MY wedding they're talking about! The Bishop died at our wedding? That's awful! Someone will have to marry us before we land - aaand it looks like Tariq is the only one who can do it. Great.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.477.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Aces, mate! Just as I was startin to get on with these lovely bride's maids, I have to fly the plane while Tariq marries Fiona and Kurt. This blows - I'm chuckin' a sickie as soon as we land!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.477.CollectSouvenir.2.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} watches]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.477.SendPlane.plane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.477.PlaceLandsideBuilding.53.name"><![CDATA[Place {number} bear balloons]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.478.name"><![CDATA[Bells Will Be Ringing 4/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.478.hint"><![CDATA[Hi there! Did you get a look at that dishy bishop? He's cute, right? I don't know what it is, but he looks so familiar. Do you think he's single? Probably not - all the good ones are taken. *Sniff*<br><br>Sorry, I'm always emotional at weddings.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.478.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Do you, Kurt, take Fiona to have and to hold from this day forward, in sickness and in health, till death do you part? I now pronounce you man and wife. You may now kiss the bride. <br><br>That was actually kind of sweet. Can we eat now? Emotions make me hungry.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.478.SellProducts.name"><![CDATA[Sell {number} goods]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.478.SendPlane.34.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Flybys]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.478.SendPlane.plane.2.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to Germany]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.478.CollectSouvenir.6.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} lipstick]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.479.name"><![CDATA[Bells Will Be Ringing 5/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.479.hint"><![CDATA[Oh dear God! I'm married - WE'RE married! Like, to each other! Kurt's gone red in the face. You can't see 'cause of his beard, but I can tell. Finally a bride! I still haven't decided if I'll take his last name. <br><br>Gotta go! It's time to throw the bouquet!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.479.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Fiona managed to throw the bouquet out of the plane as we were approaching for landing! I didn't waste a second - I grabbed a parachute and jumped after those flowers. I actually caught them, but had to spend the next couple hours hanging from the Eiffel Tower. <br><br>Yes, it was terrifying, but totally worth it - I'll be the next to get married!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.479.CollectSouvenir.15.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} flower(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.479.CollectSouvenir.48.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} medikits]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.479.SendPlane.plane.13.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to France]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.480.name"><![CDATA[The Honeymoon 1/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.480.hint"><![CDATA[Ahhh, Paris! I like totally love this city. I am so excited to be here with Kurt; I only wish that everyone else weren’t here, too. But the group hotel discount was just too sweet to pass up. Hopefully everyone will keep to themselves. I mean, they should be able to entertain themselves in Paris, right? Oh, hey – could you send a postcard to my family for me. I’ll be, err, busy for the rest of the day. ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.480.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Paris is swell an’ all, but I’m mostly happy to be married and on my honeymoon with my beloved Fifi. I’m a little worried about havin privacy … ever’ dang time I step outta the room, I find Tariq standin’ there lookin’ guilty. ]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.480.CollectSouvenir.10.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} postcard(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.480.CollectSouvenir.15.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} flower(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.480.SendPlane.helicopter.na.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} helicopters to North America]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.480.SendPlane.34.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Flybys]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.481.name"><![CDATA[The Honeymoon 2/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.481.hint"><![CDATA[THANK GOODNESS I made it off that tower in one piece. With the bouquet in hand, no less! Paris is amazing, and I want to see as much as I can but I’ve never been here and I don’t have a guide book. Fiona’s always talking about how much she loves this city … I’ll just drop by her room to see if she’s got some insider tips. Can you collect a guide book for me in the meantime? Thanks, you’re such a doll! ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.481.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[J’aime Paris: the sights, the delicious food and wine. And, ooh la la, the gorgeous Parisian women – they are in a league of their own. Even though they are breath-taking, I can’t keep my eyes off Lin. I know she turned me down, but that was ages ago. Besides what better place to go on a date than Paris? I think I’ll ask Kurt for his advice just to be sure. ]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.481.CollectSouvenir.19.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} Guide Book]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.482.name"><![CDATA[The Honeymoon 3/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.482.hint"><![CDATA[G’day, yobbos! Everyone always says how beautiful Paris, but I haven’t noticed, to be honest with ya. I’ll tell ya what’s great about Paris: THE CLUBS, mate! The food’s alright, I suppose. But the red wine is absolutely ace. My only problem is that my mouth is stained purple from all I been drinkin. I reckon Fiona knows what to do about that. While I go ask her, I need you to start some sea planes back at the airport. Thanks, cobber! ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.482.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[I am like totally flipping out! I’m supposed to be on my honeymoon, but noooooo! My co-workers are knocking on my door what feels like every 15 minutes. I’ve seen more of them here than I ever do at work. Don’t tell Kurt I told you this, but I frankly can’t wait to go home. Maybe then we can actually have some peace and quiet. ]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.482.CollectSouvenir.22.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} Coffee Machine(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.482.SendPlane.seaplane.149.name"><![CDATA[Start and send {number} Seaplanes to New Zealand]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.482.SendPlane.plane.2.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to Germany]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.483.name"><![CDATA[The Honeymoon 4/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.483.hint"><![CDATA[So, I went to Kurt for advice about Lin, but he told me to get lost. Can you imagine? I asked him if I could talk to Fiona and she said that I should treat Lin with respect and just be honest with her about my feelings. She said I should just ask Lin to dinner. I’m going to ask her out now, so wish me luck! Be a pal and grab some flowers for me, will ya? ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.483.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[ULG, Tariq is such a pig! He just asked me out again. He was actually respectful and nice. He was so lovely I was about to say yes, but then he ruined it like he always does! He said he’d make sure to order me a salad so that I can watch my girlish figure. ]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.483.CollectSouvenir.15.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} flower(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.483.CollectSouvenir.3.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} french cheeses]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.483.SendPlane.plane.na.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to North America]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.483.SendPlane.34.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Flybys]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.484.name"><![CDATA[The Honeymoon 5/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.484.hint"><![CDATA[Don’t tell Fifi, but I cain’t wait to go home. We haven’t gotten much time to ourselves – ever’ time I turn around someone from the airport is botherin’ us about somethin’. Paris is great n all, but I just wanna be alone with my wife! All we have to do is survive the flight home with those jokers! All you need to do is start the flight. ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.484.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[I never thought I would say this, but I am relieved that my honeymoon is over. Kurt and I finally get some alone time. Looks like Tariq and the gang are someone else’s problem now. ]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.484.ReturnPlane.plane.name"><![CDATA[Return {number} Flights]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.484.ReturnPlane.seaplane.name"><![CDATA[Return {number} Seaplanes]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.484.ReturnPlane.helicopter.name"><![CDATA[Return {number} helicopters]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.484.GetPassengers.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} passengers]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.485.name"><![CDATA[The Morning After 1/6]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.485.hint"><![CDATA[Mornin! Do we know each other? It’s me, Hazel Partridge. I’m the cleaning lady. Don’t recognize me? Shocker – it’s not like everyone ignores me or anything. Would you look at this place? Does anyone think to invite Hazel to the party? Nooope. And now I have to clean up after them. Great! *Sigh* I hate my life. ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.485.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[*Hick*Ouch! My head is throbbing – it feels like there’s a jackhammer inside my brain. I don’t remember anything. Where am I? These aren’t the clothes I was wearing, are they? Uuuh, I don’t feel so good. Excuse me, I think I’m gonna be sick… ]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.485.CollectSouvenir.48.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} medikits]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.485.ReturnPlane.plane.name"><![CDATA[Send back {number} planes]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.485.ReturnPlane.seaplane.name"><![CDATA[Return {number} Seaplanes]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.485.GetCargo.2.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} steak/s]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.486.name"><![CDATA[The Morning After 2/6]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.486.hint"><![CDATA[Oh la la, did you see Lin? She just stumbled out of the plane wearing a pilot’s uniform! I wonder who it belongs to. Tariq?! No way! He hasn’t got a snowball’s chance in hell with Lin.<br><br>At least I don’t think he does … ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.486.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Mornin! I just waxed this hallway and it already looks awful. Tariq ran through here, screaming his adorable little head off and then Fiona and Kurt rode through here on a motorcycle. Can you believe these animals? All that work for nothing! ]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.486.SendPlane.plane.na.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to North America]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.486.GetAirCoins.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} AirCoins]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.486.PlaceLandsideBuilding.94.name"><![CDATA[Place {number} Snack-Bar/s]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.487.name"><![CDATA[The Morning After 3/6]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.487.hint"><![CDATA[Mornin. You know what? Why should I keep workin myself to the bone when no one appreciates it. If they want this place to be a wreck, fine by me. <br><br>What’s that … HOLY CRAP! There’s a dead body in the galley! ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.487.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Oh man, I think I’m starting to remember what happened yesterday. It’s all pretty fuzzy, but still – I think we may have really done it this time. <br><br>Oh no, the cops are here! IT WASN’T ME! ]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.487.PlaceLandsideBuilding.32.name"><![CDATA[Place {number} Security Base/s]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.487.SendPlane.plane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.487.ReturnPlane.plane.name"><![CDATA[Send back {number} planes]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.488.name"><![CDATA[The Morning After 4/6]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.488.hint"><![CDATA[Well, hello. I say, this is a lovely airport you’ve got here. Don’t let me disturb you – I’ll just wander around the terminal, if that’s alright with you. It’s a great place to people watch. <br><br>Wow, your cleaning lady is a busy bee. Goodness, she appears to be white as a sheet. Now she’s screaming. AHHH! Why is she running towards me? WHY IS SHE HITTING ME? ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.488.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Aaahhh! That was … the dead man I found in the galley! What’s happening? First the police surround the entire airport and then dead bodies are moseying through the terminal. I may be old and kind of confused right now, but don’t you worry – as long as I can swing a mop, no harm will come to anyone. ]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.488.SendPlane.plane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.488.GetPassengers.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} passengers]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.488.SendPlane.34.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} flyby(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.489.name"><![CDATA[The Morning After 5/6]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.489.hint"><![CDATA[Mornin! At first I thought Tariq and Kurt were worried about what to do with the old man, but I was wrong. They don’t care at all. So I locked him up in my supply closet, where the body was before it came back alive. Anyway don’t worry, boss. I’ve got everything under control. ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.489.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Why, I never! I came here to retrieve my twin brother’s earthly remains – bless him *sniff* – and that harpy attacked me and locked me in a closet with my dead brother! <br><br> You’ll be hearing from me again, I promise you! You’d better have a good lawyer. ]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.489.SendPlane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.489.GetAirCoins.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} AirCoins]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.489.GetPassengers.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} passengers]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.490.name"><![CDATA[The Morning After 6/6]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.490.hint"><![CDATA[Blaargh! Three days in the clink. They allowed me one phone call, so thankfully I was able to postpone my date. That Hazel Partridge better stay outta my way!<br><br> I realized on the flight home, if I just keep drinking, then I never have to think about that poor Bishop. *Sigh* I need a vacation. ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.490.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Mornin! Anyone else noticed that Tariq’s in a miserable mood? You make one lousy mistake and everyone’s pouting like little children. What do they expect? No one tells me anything! <br><br>Hey you! What’re you lookin at? Never seen someone workin before? Outta my way – I gotta mop. ]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.490.GetAirCoins.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} AirCoins]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.490.GetCargo.14.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} cotton]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.490.GetPassengers.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} passengers]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.490.SendPlane.seaplane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Seaplanes]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.491.name"><![CDATA[First Time for Everything 1/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.491.hint"><![CDATA[Hey, buddy! I was checking out the personal ads in the paper and I came across one that sounded right up my alley: “Hot Mama seeks Cool Daddy-o – Older woman with lots of spunk is searching for the man of her dreams …” Sounds like she described me to a tee. I gotta answer this ad before someone else beats me to the punch. Can you fill in for me while I write my response? ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.491.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[G’day! Went on a rager yesterday arvo and it looks like I accidentally posted a personal ad in the paper while I was blotto. Now my inbox is choked with responses from blokes interested in takin me out. One of ‘em ain’t too bad: “Hands-on pilot anxious to have a look at your engine …” Here’s hopin he’s not a total drongo! ]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.491.SendPlane.plane.178.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to Thailand]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.491.SendPlane.helicopter.13.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} helicopters to France]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.491.ReturnPlane.name"><![CDATA[Return {number} flights]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.491.GetPassengers.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} passengers]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.492.name"><![CDATA[First Time for Everything 2/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.492.hint"><![CDATA[Hot Mama and I have exchanged a few e-mails and I think there could be something there. Some of her messages were pretty suggestive, if not downright offensive. I wonder if that’s how I make women feel sometimes … NAH, can’t be!<br><br>Regardless, I don’t want to let her slip through my fingers. What if she’s the one?! ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.492.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Crikey, this is gettin serious! I think I know who I’ve been chatting with, but I hope I’m wrong. I’m getting’ heaps cranky, mate … what are you lookin at? Yeah, you! ]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.492.PlaceLandsideBuilding.4.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} bus station(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.492.GetPassengers.name"><![CDATA[Visit {number} different airports and collect passengers.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.492.ReturnPlane.37.name"><![CDATA[Return {number} cashcows]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.492.PlaceLandsideBuilding.92.name"><![CDATA[Place {number} Rest-Rooms]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.493.name"><![CDATA[First Time for Everything 3/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.493.hint"><![CDATA[Evenin‘, chief! You’re not gonna believe what just happened. I’ve been breaking my back, polishing these floors and, just as I’m about to pack it in for the day, Tariq tears around the corner like a house on fire and destroys me day’s work. But do I complain? Nooooo. I swear, I no one respects me around here. Can you help me spruce things up? ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.493.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Almost time for my date! What do you think – do I look like a stud or what? So, I took a closer look at my love letters and I’m pretty sure I have dates with two different women. You only live once, right? ]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.493.CollectSouvenir.14.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} candy/candies]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.493.SendPlane.plane.85.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to Wyoming]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.493.SendPlane.plane.38.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s) to Croatia]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.494.name"><![CDATA[First Time for Everything 4/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.494.hint"><![CDATA[Hi there, kitten! Don’t be cross, but I don’t have time to chat today. I just had the worst date of my life and the only thing I feel like doing is putting on my PJs and watching a stupid movie. Oh and, whatever you do, NEVER date a pilot. Promise? ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.494.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[So, that was … different. Listen, whatever you do, never fish off the company pier. NEVER! You understand what I’m getting at? It’ll only end in disaster. ]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.494.ReturnPlane.11.name"><![CDATA[Return {number} SeaRama Solo/s]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.494.SellProducts.name"><![CDATA[Sell {number} goods]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.494.ReturnPlane.helicopter.name"><![CDATA[Service {number} helicopters]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.495.name"><![CDATA[First Time for Everything 5/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.495.hint"><![CDATA[Sorry about what date? My date hasn’t even started yet. You know who I just saw crawling out of some club? Lin and Cassandra! Normally they get along fine, but they’re looking quite miffed. Anyway, my “double dose” of woman should be here any minute. That means two ladies are showing up, right? Thought so … ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.495.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Hmph, my sweetie-pie hasn’t shown up yet. There must be something in the air today, because Hazel Whatshername has been waiting for her date to show up forever now. Apparently, she’s got a date with a hot pilot. She said he’s a real cool Daddy-o … poor guy. He has no idea what he’s in for. Wait a minute … Cool Daddy-O? OH NO … HAZEL PARTRIDGE?! HEEELLLLLLP! ]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.495.CollectSouvenir.35.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} Bikinis]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.495.GetCargo.9.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} eggs]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.495.CollectSouvenir.33.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} sun glasses]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.495.ReturnPlane.plane.name"><![CDATA[Send back {number} planes]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.496.name"><![CDATA[Tête-à-Tariq 1/3]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.496.hint"><![CDATA[Don’t get me wrong, Hazel Partridge is a whole lot of woman – but I think she’s a tad too much for my taste. I can’t admit that it was a misunderstanding, cause then no one will ever go out with me again. But if I go out with her, I’ll lose my cred as a lady’s man. Maybe I can invite her to a fancy schmancy restaurant and she’ll lose her nerve and back out? ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.496.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[I always thought Tariq was a zero, but turns out he’s a class act. I actually wanted to go clubbing with him but he brought me to this fancy French restaurant “Le Gourmand” instead. And I ain’t one to turn down free food. If Tariq sends me home with his leftovers, I’ll be the happiest cleaning lady at the airport.  ]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.496.SendPlane.13.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} flight(s) to France]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.496.PlaceLandsideBuilding.76.name"><![CDATA[Place {number} large hotels]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.496.GetAirCoins.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} aircoin/s]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.497.name"><![CDATA[Tête-à-Tariq 2/3]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.497.hint"><![CDATA[Cold feet? No such luck. Partridge is just now washing down her five plates of foie gras with wine and cheese. She’s a bottomless pit, that woman. Know what she did a few minutes ago? She gave the waiter a high five when he brought out her food! The only thing that could be worse, is if my parents were he… Mom! What are you doing here? ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.497.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Mmmm, this creep suzette is to die for. So delicate yet so fluffly. And the presentation? Absolutely theatrical. Oh and the cream, pillowy and soft like clouds. Tariq’s parents? Yeah, they were here. They left in an awful hurry. Nice enough, I suppose. The dad was going on about how he “his son was dead to him.” I didn’t know Tariq had siblings. ]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.497.GetAirCoins.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} aircoin/s]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.497.SellProducts.name"><![CDATA[Sell {number} products]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.498.name"><![CDATA[Tête-à-Tariq 3/3]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.498.hint"><![CDATA[Ok, my parents may have disowned me, but at least the whole ordeal is behind me. It could have been worse, you know. We could have been their millionth customers. Imagine that! Me and that ogre on the cover of a newspaper, being carted off on some trip around the world? Knock on wood, eh? ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.498.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[I don’t believe it! We were headed out the door when suddenly were blinded by a flash of confetti. Then the flash of cameras. Then the announcement: Congratulations, you’re our millionth customers and we’re sending you on a trip around the world! It was like a dream … ]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.498.SendPlane.na.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} flight(s) to North America]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.498.BuyLandsideBuilding.151.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} Viva Skyrama-Towers]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.498.GetAirCoins.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} aircoin/s]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.499.name"><![CDATA[Around the World 1/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.499.hint"><![CDATA[This is a nightmare – a trip around the world with Hazel Partridge. I thought about declining, but I know I can’t do that. Besides, it might be nice to have someone flying me all over the world instead of the other way around. *Sigh* First stop, Venice.  ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.499.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Hey, you seen Tariq anywhere? He is fit to be tied. So I accidentally knocked him out of the gondola when I bent over to find my chocolate bar – I can’t be expected to know where my rear end is at all times. Real women know how to create waves, know what I mean? ]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.499.SendPlane.plane.7.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to Italy]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.499.SendPlane.27.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-M-Cargos to Italy]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.499.SendPlane.seaplane.7.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} seaplanes to Italy]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.499.SendPlane.helicopter.7.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} helicopters to Italy]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.500.name"><![CDATA[Around the World 2/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.500.hint"><![CDATA[*Achoo!* Ulg, I hate Venice. I’m stuck here in this hospital watching Italian soap operas, while Partridge is out soaking up the sites. <br><br>Let’s just get on with this, ok? And please, no more romantic trips! ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.500.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Greetings from the North Pole! This is a real winter wonderland – it’s like bein inside a snow globe. You’d think it was torture, lookin at Tariq. What a spoiled sport! It’s „Leave me alone“ this and „I’ve got the flu“ that. What a sissy. If he doesn’t cheer up here soon, I’ll just have to make him. ]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.500.SendPlane.plane.75.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to Greenland]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.500.SendPlane.27.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-M-Cargos to Greenland]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.500.SendPlane.seaplane.75.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} sea planes to Greenland]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.501.name"><![CDATA[Around the World 3/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.501.hint"><![CDATA[Omg, have you heard? Tariq and Ms. Partridge are like totally in love. Tariq looks like he’s been shot by cupid’s arrow. His cheeks were flushed and it looked like he had butterflies all over. They just got back from the North Pole? Ew, that’s not romantic!<br><br>I’ll surprise them with a get-away to the most romantic place on earth: Germany. ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.501.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[I can’t do this anymore! Fiona sent us to my home town and now my parents and friends think I’m really with this Partridge hag. Know what my father just did? Slapped me heartily on the back and gave me a sly wink. What does that mean?! ]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.501.SendPlane.plane.sa.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to South America]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.501.SendPlane.plane.2.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to Germany]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.502.name"><![CDATA[Around the World 4/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.502.hint"><![CDATA[So, dude. I know how I’m gonna ditch this sea witch Hazel. We can create a diversion while we’re boarding so that Partridge gets on a flight to Siberia or so. Meanwhile, I’ll be on the right plane headed for the warm waters of the Caribbean. Fool-proof!  ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.502.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[What the ...?!? You fool! You sent both planes to the same destination? Do I have to do anything myself here? Whatever, I'll go to the beach to show of my sixpack. ]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.502.SendPlane.plane.131.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to Haiti]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.503.name"><![CDATA[Around the World 5/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.503.hint"><![CDATA[This is what I’m talkin about: beaches full of hot babes as far as the eye can see. Look over there – there’s even an exclusive celebrity beach. Oh my … is that a beached whale? I’ve got to help. Take a picture: women go nuts for this stuff! ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.503.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Hey. I knew it – Tariq is a pig just like every other man. I was just minding my own business, workin on my base tan, when that idiot attacked me and dragged me into the water. Someone jerk even took a picture and we made the paper – again! ]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.503.GetAirCoins.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} AirCoins]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.503.GetPassengers.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} passengers]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.504.name"><![CDATA[Dear Jeanette 1/3]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.504.hint"><![CDATA[What? No, Hazel Partridge and I are NOT together! The pictures in the papers make it seem like we are the airport’s dream couple. I’ll have to pretend to break up with her – that’s the only way to put these nasty rumors to bed. No pun intended! ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.504.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Let it never be said that I am a dolt. My plan to get rid of that old dust rag is nothing short of genius. Seriously, nothing can go wrong. I’ve already drafted the text message… ]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.504.1"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to America]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.504.2"><![CDATA[ Send {number} helicopters to Asia]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.504.3"><![CDATA[Return {number} flight(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.504.4"><![CDATA[Collect {number} passengers]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.505.name"><![CDATA[Dear Jeanette 2/3]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.505.hint"><![CDATA[She hasn’t answered my text! How can I break up with her if she’s ignoring me? Who does she think she is anyway? I’m a catch – practically an adonis. I ought to give her a piece of mind … that’s just what I’m gonna do!  ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.505.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Tariq’s been sending me those phone messages non-stop. I don’t have time for that mess so I’ve been ignoring them. I hope he doesn’t think we’re a couple. Don’t get me wrong, the vacation was nice. But I can do a lot better than Tariq.  ]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.505.1"><![CDATA[Send {number} cargoplanes to Russia]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.505.2"><![CDATA[Collect {number} Flower Circles ]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.505.3"><![CDATA[Place {number} Flower Arches]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.505.4"><![CDATA[Collect {number} teddy bear(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.506.name"><![CDATA[Dear Jeanette 3/3]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.506.hint"><![CDATA[Tariq’s lost it! He followed me all over the airport on his moped. Wants to know why I haven’t answered his texts. Normally I have a thing for morons, but Tariq is too much for me. If he doesn’t lay off, I’m gonna set him straight! ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.506.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[What the … she broke up with me. SHE broke up with ME. Per text message. Just like that. Pssh, whatever. I’m out of her leage anyway. I’m smart and handsome and … so alone! *sniff* ]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.506.1"><![CDATA[Place {number} cactus/cacti 2]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.506.2"><![CDATA[Collect {number} candies]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.506.3"><![CDATA[Collect {number} teddy bear(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.506.4"><![CDATA[Collect {number} candies]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.507.name"><![CDATA[All’s Fair in Love and War 1/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.507.hint"><![CDATA[I am pretty bummed. Hazel ruined everything when she broke up with me. If anyone is breaking up with anyone, it’s me with her! Help me win her back by sending a couple flybys her way? I have to make things right! ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.507.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Hey darlin! Isn’t that sweet? Tariq sent some flybys to win me back. He’ll never change. What can I say? He just can’t live without … Hazel Partridge? That TROLL? Oh, we’ll just see about that, Miss Toilet Brush! ]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.507.1"><![CDATA[Collect {number} swim shorts]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.507.2"><![CDATA[Collect {number} Bikinis]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.507.3"><![CDATA[Send {number} flyby(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.508.name"><![CDATA[All’s Fair in Love and War 2/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.508.hint"><![CDATA[Hey there! Have you seen my new beau? He’s a perfect 10 – pilot, underwear model, extreme athlete. He’s a dream man for a woman with needs. Did you see the flybys? It was my honey bunny, of course. I want to do something romantic for him to say thank you. Will you help me? ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.508.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Hi there, cream puff! There are heart balloons all over the place – looks like Hazel and Tariq are really in love. It’s funny, but it doesn’t bother me anymore. Really! NOT BOTHERED.  ]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.508.1"><![CDATA[Place {number} Rest-Rooms]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.508.2"><![CDATA[Place {number} Beach Bars]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.508.3"><![CDATA[Collect {number} lipstick(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.508.4"><![CDATA[Collect {number} batteries]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.509.name"><![CDATA[All’s Fair in Love and War 3/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.509.hint"><![CDATA[Well, hello there. Isn’t this just a lovely day? Can you do me a favor, snugglepus? Great! All you have to do is get everyone out of the airport and start some planes for flybys. Two can play at this game… ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.509.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[HA! My plan is working. Did you see the flybys? “Have dinner with me? XO, L.“ Got my hair slicked back, wearing my favorite fish net muscle shirt. Lin won’t be able to resist me – time to head to the restaurant. This is gonna be fun! ]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.509.1"><![CDATA[Collect {number} passengers]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.509.2"><![CDATA[Send {number} helicopters to Thailand]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.509.3"><![CDATA[Send {number} flyby(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.510.name"><![CDATA[All’s Fair in Love and War 4/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.510.hint"><![CDATA[G’day! I just scored the sweetest gig ever – I’ll be piloting a private jet to Vegas for Hazel and Adonis. Weird names, but they seem to be in love, so who I am to judge. All I really care about is the club scene, which is supposed to be ace in Vegas. Can’t wait! ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.510.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Oh no! Hazel and Adonis?! Two more weeks of these sappy drongos! And the pictures – I’ll never be able to forget the pictures.  ]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.510.1"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to America]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.510.2"><![CDATA[Collect {number} cameras]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.510.3"><![CDATA[Collect {number} lipstick]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.510.4"><![CDATA[Collect {number} AirCoins]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.511.name"><![CDATA[All’s Fair in Love and War 5/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.511.hint"><![CDATA[Tonight’s the night. I’ll walk into the cafe, cool and confident. I’ll rip off my fish net shirt and proclaim my love to her and her heart will be mine. I can just see her face now, but I don’t want to wait any longer. It’s now or never! ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.511.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[…<br><br>…<br><br>…<br><br>… [to be continued]]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.511.1"><![CDATA[Send {number} flights to Belgium]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.511.2"><![CDATA[Place {number} large hotels]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.main.511.3"><![CDATA[Collect {number} passengers]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.512.name"><![CDATA[Match Made on the Runway 1/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.512.hint"><![CDATA[I don’t know if you’ve heard the news, but I split up with Adonis recently. I needed some space – he was way too clingy for my taste. Besides, I can do better. ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.512.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[*Sniff* I know I broke up with him, but I do kinda miss Doni. Hard work is the only cure for heartache – I’ll make these floors shine like mirrors! ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.513.name"><![CDATA[Match Made on the Runway 2/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.513.hint"><![CDATA[You seen Cassie lately? She was grinning like the cat that ate the canary. She was even whistling! I wonder what’s gotten into her lately… ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.513.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[I just saw Cassandra and she was staring at me like a love-sick puppy dog. *Sigh* What can I say? I am a pilot magnet! ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.514.name"><![CDATA[Match Made on the Runway 3/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.514.hint"><![CDATA[G’day! I’m happier than a croc in a sunny bogey-hole – I have a new Sheila! We’re takin' things slow, cause she just broke up with her bloke, but I have a good feelin about this one. Her blood’s worth bottlin!
<br><br>...Yes, or boots. I suppose it is boots, nowadays. ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.514.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[I’m doing much better now, thanks. In fact, things couldn’t be better. I’ve found the perfect distraction! ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.515.name"><![CDATA[Match Made on the Runway 4/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.515.hint"><![CDATA[Ulg, have you seen Cassandra and Partridge lately? I HATE new couples. They are disgusting. *sob* I’m so… LONELY! That reminds me – I wonder what my ex is up to these days? ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.515.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[You will never guess who asked me out the other day. In fact, don’t even try. Call me crazy, but I said yes! ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.516.name"><![CDATA[Match Made on the Runway 5/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.516.hint"><![CDATA[Dude, there should be like a policy or something that forbids pilots from hooking up with other airport employees. This is getting totally ridiculous! ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.516.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[What? Gross! Why would I ever go out with Tariq again? Truth be told, I think he turned me off of men for good! I am going out with Cassandra. Obviously. ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.517.name"><![CDATA[Cross My Heart 1/3]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.517.hint"><![CDATA[Some idiot tracked their big idiot footprints across my wet floors! It must have been Tara – she has always disrespected my art. Besides, no one else wears size 11 heels! ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.517.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Being the classy woman I am, I invited Tara to dinner to talk about this face-to-face. But I am also no dummy, so we’re meeting in a nice restaurant so she can’t make a scene. ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.518.name"><![CDATA[Cross My Heart 2/3]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.518.hint"><![CDATA[I’ve always wanted to take Cassandra for a spin, if you know what I mean. Now I’ve got a fail-proof plan to get her to go out with me. She won’t say no – you’ll see. ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.518.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[I have to tell you something… I invited Tariq to dinner. Hear me out! We never talked about what happened in the café that day. It’s just to talk, I promise. ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.519.name"><![CDATA[Cross My Heart 3/3]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.519.hint"><![CDATA[Welp, this is gonna be interesting. Looks like I have three dates at the same restaurant at the same time. Can’t say I’m surprised really, but I will need your help. I’m only human, after all. ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.519.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Psst, hey… it’s me: Tariq! Almost mistook me for Tara, eh? Well, I dress to impress. Operation Down Under Romance is underway. "Tara" has a date with Cassie tonight. I also have dates with Hazel and Lin lined up in the same joint. Don’t worry; I’ve got this all under control. ]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.520.name"><![CDATA[Dinner Date 1/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.520.hint"><![CDATA[Where in the hell is Tara? She should be here by now. Great – is that Tariq? OH NO! He’s headed this way! Not now…]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.520.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Why is this loon jumping down my throat when she’s the one who invited me to dinner? Unless… do you think she meant to invite Tara? In that case, I’ll give her what she wants. I’ll be right back!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.521.name"><![CDATA[Dinner Date 2/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.521.hint"><![CDATA[Where is he, that bastard? I’ve been waiting here forever. I know he’s here – I saw him at Hazel’s table. Once a player, always a player.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.521.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Sorry to have kept you waiting. But I’m here now, so what did you want to talk about?]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.522.name"><![CDATA[Dinner Date 3/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.522.hint"><![CDATA[Tara? What’s going on here? I’ve been waiting for you! Are… are you cheating on me with Lin?!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.522.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Yikes, those two are really at each other’s throats. I’ll just be under this table until this cat fight blows over.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.523.name"><![CDATA[Dinner Date 4/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.523.hint"><![CDATA[*Sigh* I need to sort out my love life. Nothing helps me clear my head like a big bowl of champagne sorbet with caviar… whoa, why is Hazel here? And more importantly, why does it look like she’s about to rip my head off?]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.523.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[There are you, you coward! What’s the matter: can’t handle your problems on your own? Gotta send Tariq to do you dirty work? Figures!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.524.name"><![CDATA[Dinner Date 5/5]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.524.hint"><![CDATA[Why are Tara and Hazel screaming at each other? Shouldn’t she be hiding under Lin’s table on the other side of the restaurant? Just what in the hell is goin on here?  Why are there two Taras? And why does that one have such hairy legs?]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.524.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Crap. This did not work out the way I planned. At all. I better get outta here fast before they all kick my butt.]]></item>
  
   <item name="av.goal.main.525.name"><![CDATA[Tariq on Ten 1/3]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.525.hint"><![CDATA[Great. Everyone’s making fun of me for being a cross-dresser. How insensitive! Besides, men do not come manlier than me. Just wait – I’ll show them and I’ll start by planting a tree.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.525.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Ummm, what the hell? What genius planted a tree in the middle of the runway? Kurt, lemme borrow you axe. I’ll totally bring it right back, I promise.]]></item>
  
  <item name="av.goal.main.526.name"><![CDATA[Tariq on Ten 2/3]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.526.hint"><![CDATA[Tree planted! Next I will build a house. But why stop at one? Why not build a whole complex – I can see it now: Tariq Town, for the burliest of the burly.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.526.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[What in tarnation? What’s that smoldering heap of rubble over there? And who spent all this money on housing?]]></item>
  
   <item name="av.goal.main.527.name"><![CDATA[Tariq on Ten 3/3]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.527.hint"><![CDATA[I’m already feeling manlier, which I didn’t even think was possible. Next step: father a son. You know? With my sexual history, I’d be shocked if I hadn’t already fathered a child. I’ll pay some of my exes a visit to find out.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.527.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Weird. They’ve all moved and left no forwarding contact information…]]></item>
  
   <item name="av.goal.main.528.name"><![CDATA[Family Man 1/6]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.528.hint"><![CDATA[Since I couldn’t find my son, I’ve decided to become a foster parent. Take in a kid who needs a good home. I’ll head there after my twelve hour shift – the things we do for our kids. Being a single parent is tough, but rewarding.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.528.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Pleasure to meet you! Tad is my name and I am Tariq’s new boy. I do so look forward to learning all he has to teach me about aviation, love, loss and life in general.]]></item>
  
   <item name="av.goal.main.529.name"><![CDATA[Family Man 2/6]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.529.hint"><![CDATA[That little kiss-ass! He’s got all these simps at the airport fawning over him. Does he think this is a contest? If it’s a contest he wants, it’s a contest he’ll get!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.529.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[I was just talking to Tad, Tariq’s lovely foster son, when – for no reason at all – Tariq snuck up behind him and gave him an atomic wedgie! Seriously, what is wrong with him?]]></item>
  
   <item name="av.goal.main.530.name"><![CDATA[Family Man 3/6]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.530.hint"><![CDATA[ It’s no big deal, really! That Mr. Tariq, he is quite the rapscallion. Life’s too short to cry over atomic wedgies. Plus, I have so much to be grateful for – I have a roof over my head, clothes on my back and a date with my new gentlewoman companion!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.530.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[I know I said I’d retired my pumps, but I am back as Tara one more time to teach that insufferable show-off Tad a lesson. *grins devilishly*]]></item>
  
   <item name="av.goal.main.531.name"><![CDATA[Family Man 4/6]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.531.hint"><![CDATA[I... I was dressed as Tara and I passed Tad in the hallway – who was talking to this super-hot girl, I might add – and do you know what he did, the bum? He smiled, waved and said, “Good day, Mr. Tariq.” Show off!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.531.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[I’ve got a plant to take that Tad down a peg or two. I’ll invite him on a double date, steal his date and prove once and for all how much more alpha I am. Perfect! I’m sure if I asked Lin to go with me, she’d be desperate enough to say yes.]]></item>
  
   <item name="av.goal.main.532.name"><![CDATA[Family Man 5/6]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.532.hint"><![CDATA[*epic eye roll* Tariq begged me to go on a double date with him and Tad. Normally, I’d say no, but I’ve heard so many good things about Tad that I’ve been dying to meet him.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.532.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Dang it! My girlfriend can’t make it tonight – she’s going on a mission trip to Guatemala. But I already agreed to go and I am a young man of my word. Plus, he invited that lovely cleaning lady I’ve heard so much about. I’m really looking forward to getting to know her.]]></item>
  
   <item name="av.goal.main.533.name"><![CDATA[Family Man 6/6]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.533.hint"><![CDATA[I don’t believe this crap! Tad and Hazel get along like bosom buddies. There’s no fooling this creep. I know – I’ll adopt him out of spite. That way I’ll have all the time in the world to put him in his place.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.533.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Look, Mr. Tariq – I think you know as well as I do that this isn’t working out. It’s me, not you. Don’t worry, I’ve found a nice couple of female pilots who want to adopt me!]]></item>
  
   <item name="av.goal.main.534.name"><![CDATA[Man’s Best Friend 1/3]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.534.hint"><![CDATA[I’ve never been so depressed in my life. Nobody loves me and I’m gonna die alone. Might as well accept my fate and get a dog. Wait – chicks dig dudes with dogs! Maybe I could convince Lin to help me take care of my new pooch…]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.534.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Tariq is unbelievable! He dropped his dog off with a note saying that he wants me to help him raise it. The poor thing ran away! What now?]]></item>
  
   <item name="av.goal.main.535.name"><![CDATA[Man’s Best Friend 2/3]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.535.hint"><![CDATA[Rrruff ruff! Bow yippie wow – grrrrrrrrr. Woof, bark bark!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.535.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[What in tarnation is going on here? Our airport is in ruins because you decided to take orders from a dang dog. How’d you even understand it? We can’t afford this right now!]]></item>
  
   <item name="av.goal.main.536.name"><![CDATA[Man’s Best Friend 3/3]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.536.hint"><![CDATA[You found my puppy dog! Thanks, man. Don’t worry about Kurt – he’s always grumpy. I’ll do some overtime to take care of that bill. Rover’s worth the trouble and I can always ask him mommy Lin to help out.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.main.536.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[I’m so glad you found the dog, but he’s a complete mess. Stinky, kinda ugly and he’s not fully house-broken yet. He really does need someone to take care of him, just like Rover the doggy. I see now how much Tariq needs me!]]></item>
  
  
  
 </category>
</language>
