<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<language>
 <category name="av.news">
  <item name="av.news.header"><![CDATA[Skyrama News]]></item>
  <item name="av.news.title"><![CDATA[Hi there! I'm Cassandra your new seaplane pilot. Let me give you a quick overlook of the new content and features.]]></item>
  <item name="av.news.text"><![CDATA[<li>The new Cargo System has arrived! Stick to the new tutorial to learn more about it!</li><li>Passengers collected during a single day will leave your airport after 72 hours, unless you send them! Always keep that in mind!</li>]]></item>
  <item name="av.news.hint_title"><![CDATA[Hint:]]></item>
  <item name="av.news.hint_text"><![CDATA[If your planes are serviced at other airports you will get twice the reward!]]></item>
  <item name="av.news.shop_title"><![CDATA[WonderQuicky!]]></item>
  <item name="av.news.shop_text"><![CDATA[Collect plane parts to complete the WonderQuicky collection!!!]]></item>
 </category>
 <category name="av.santanews">
  <item name="av.santanews.header"><![CDATA[Winter News]]></item>
  <item name="av.santanews.title"><![CDATA[Ho ho ho! In the winter weeks pilots, stewards and passengers all look forward to the big party at the end of the year. A lot of new things are waiting for you!]]></item>
  <item name="av.santanews.text"><![CDATA[During the winter weeks santa flies by! Look out - maybe he will drop some gifts - try to collect them and you may get rewarded! Available from 24.12. to 26.12!]]></item>
  <item name="av.santanews.hint_title"><![CDATA[Fireworks!!!]]></item>
  <item name="av.santanews.hint_text"><![CDATA[Happy new year! Send the brand new firework flyby to your buddies. Available from 29.12. to 31.12!]]></item>
  <item name="av.santanews.shop_title"><![CDATA[All you can quickservice:]]></item>
  <item name="av.santanews.shop_text"><![CDATA[Pay once and then service as much as you can within 24 hours for FREE.]]></item>
 </category>
 <category name="av.january12news">
  <item name="av.january12news.header"><![CDATA[New Year's News]]></item>
  <item name="av.january12news.title"><![CDATA[Happy new Year! Welcome back in 2012 - May all planes be serviced instantly, may a lot of passengers come to your airport and may the Aircoin be with you!]]></item>
  <item name="av.january12news.text"><![CDATA[Because of technical improvements planes are now automatically moved to their respective bay. Try it out and you will notice that this feature makes sending planes a lot more comfortable and is a mature improvement for every airport manager!]]></item>
  <item name="av.january12news.hint_title"><![CDATA[Updates:]]></item>
  <item name="av.january12news.hint_text"><![CDATA[We are working hard on improving the loading time and performance issues. True story!]]></item>
  <item name="av.january12news.shop_title"><![CDATA[Buy Goods:]]></item>
  <item name="av.january12news.shop_text"><![CDATA[You are out of goods? Feel free to buy them in the shop's special category]]></item>
 </category>
 <category name="av.modernizationnews">
  <item name="av.modernizationnews.header"><![CDATA[New Daily Quests!]]></item>
  <item name="av.modernizationnews.title"><![CDATA[Time for takeoff! 21 brand new adventures for airport managers!]]></item>
  <item name="av.modernizationnews.text"><![CDATA[Remodeling such a massive airport is no light undertaking. The entire Skyrama crew has been working overtime the past few months, but now Tariq, Lin, Kurt and the whole gang are back and ready to get going. Go on the shopping spree you always wanted or take a romantic excursion with that special someone. Click the star to the left and prepare for liftoff. Be sure to tackle the new quests right away, as a new quest event will replace them in just a few weeks.]]></item>
  <item name="av.modernizationnews.hint_title"><![CDATA[Updates:]]></item>
  <item name="av.modernizationnews.hint_text"><![CDATA[Place tech-decorations next to bays to reduce their service time by max. 40%.]]></item>
  <item name="av.modernizationnews.shop_title"><![CDATA[New Planes!]]></item>
  <item name="av.modernizationnews.shop_text"><![CDATA[Check out the brand new prototype and safety aircrafts in your shop.]]></item>
 </category>
 <category name="av.modernizationnews+mmo">
  <item name="av.modernizationnews+mmo.header"><![CDATA[The Airport of Tomorrow!]]></item>
  <item name="av.modernizationnews+mmo.title"><![CDATA[The airport of tomorrow is here! We have some great prototype planes and fancy new buildings coming our way.]]></item>
  <item name="av.modernizationnews+mmo.text"><![CDATA[Listen up pilots! Skyrama is nomitated for the "Best Tycoon Browser MMO"! Hoooray!!! Please use this link below and vote for us! <br/><a href="http://mmooftheyear.com/" target="_blank"><u>Link to MMO-Votings</u></a><br/>Help Skyrama reach even higher altitudes!! A surprise is waiting for you, if we win this award!]]></item>
  <item name="av.modernizationnews+mmo.hint_title"><![CDATA[Updates:]]></item>
  <item name="av.modernizationnews+mmo.hint_text"><![CDATA[Place tech-decorations next to bays to reduce their service time by max. 40%.]]></item>
  <item name="av.modernizationnews+mmo.shop_title"><![CDATA[New Planes!]]></item>
  <item name="av.modernizationnews+mmo.shop_text"><![CDATA[Check out the brand new prototype and safety aircrafts in your shop.]]></item>
 </category>
 <category name="av.modernizationnews+unlocking">
  <item name="av.modernizationnews+unlocking.header"><![CDATA[The Airport of Tomorrow!]]></item>
  <item name="av.modernizationnews+unlocking.title"><![CDATA[The airport of tomorrow is here! We have some great prototype planes and fancy new buildings coming our way.]]></item>
  <item name="av.modernizationnews+unlocking.text"><![CDATA[Listen up pilots!<br/>You can now track your flight-progress with the new country-unlocking flightmap.<br/>Visit each country in a continent to get a reward and show your awesome planes to players all over the world!]]></item>
  <item name="av.modernizationnews+unlocking.hint_title"><![CDATA[Updates:]]></item>
  <item name="av.modernizationnews+unlocking.hint_text"><![CDATA[Place tech-decorations next to bays to reduce their service time by max. 40%.]]></item>
  <item name="av.modernizationnews+unlocking.shop_title"><![CDATA[New Planes!]]></item>
  <item name="av.modernizationnews+unlocking.shop_text"><![CDATA[Check out the brand new prototype and safety aircrafts in your shop.]]></item>
 </category>
 <category name="av.zeppelinexpedition">
  <item name="av.zeppelinexpedition.header"><![CDATA[New Features!]]></item>
  <item name="av.zeppelinexpedition.title"><![CDATA[Our airport is ready to host the famous Zeppelin Expedition and Country Unlocking! Fame, honor and some very special rewards await all attendees!]]></item>
  <item name="av.zeppelinexpedition.text"><![CDATA[You can now track your flight-progress with the new country-unlocking flightmap.Visit each country in a continent to get a reward and show your awesome planes to players all over the world!<br/><br/>Once you got your zeppelin hangar you can start to collect fuel for your expedition by completing the AIRSHOW mini game. When you collected enough fuel you can send your zeppelin to exotic places to collect rare souvenirs. Collect enough souvenirs and you can trade them for one of two very exclusive planes. Check your storage, maybe your zeppelin hangar is allready there!]]></item>
  <item name="av.zeppelinexpedition.hint_title"><![CDATA[Zeppelin Expedition!]]></item>
  <item name="av.zeppelinexpedition.hint_text"><![CDATA[Get the Dedarama or the incredible Spaceship-One as a reward for the expedition collection.]]></item>
  <item name="av.zeppelinexpedition.shop_title"><![CDATA[Airshow]]></item>
  <item name="av.zeppelinexpedition.shop_text"><![CDATA[The Airshow appears on your airport as soon as you have a zeppelin hangar. Click on the planes passing by in the right moment to get your fuel!]]></item>
 </category>
 <category name="av.mmo">
  <item name="av.mmo.header"><![CDATA[MMO of the year!]]></item>
  <item name="av.mmo.title"><![CDATA[Let your voice be heard and you could be a winner! Thanks to your votes the Skyrama crew recently walked away with the MMO Award 2012.]]></item>
  <item name="av.mmo.text"><![CDATA[You voted us the best tycoon browser game in the <br/><a href="http://mmooftheyear.com/" target="_blank"><u>MMO of the Year 2012</u></a><br/> competition! We’ll be popping bottles of the bubbly and you'll get three new amazing gifts! All true crack pilots need space to spread their wings, which is why the ground crew has been toiling around the clock to free up an additional slot in your small hangar. And it’s all on the house!]]></item>
  <item name="av.mmo.hint_title"><![CDATA[Your lucky star]]></item>
  <item name="av.mmo.hint_text"><![CDATA[This new decorative piece will have your airport gleaming night and day.]]></item>
  <item name="av.mmo.shop_title"><![CDATA[10’s the lucky number!]]></item>
  <item name="av.mmo.shop_text"><![CDATA[9 is good, 10 is awesome! That’s why we’re giving you 10 free spins on the Lucky Luggage!]]></item>
 </category>
 <category name="av.superfuel">
  <item name="av.superfuel.header"><![CDATA[Pump your planes full of Super Fuel]]></item>
  <item name="av.superfuel.title"><![CDATA[Break the speed of sound with the brand new Super Fuel!]]></item>
  <item name="av.superfuel.text"><![CDATA[Are your planes, helicopters and jets seemingly glued to the ground? Not at your airport! Fill up on Super Fuel and watch your fleet zoom through the air visiting friends and delivering invaluable commodities all around the world.]]></item>
  <item name="av.superfuel.hint_title"><![CDATA[VIP Landing]]></item>
  <item name="av.superfuel.hint_text"><![CDATA[Holding positions are a thing of the past. Land your plane without delay.]]></item>
  <item name="av.superfuel.shop_title"><![CDATA[Fill 'em up!]]></item>
  <item name="av.superfuel.shop_text"><![CDATA[For everyone above level 3 - 50 units of Super Fuel for free!]]></item>
 </category>
 <category name="av.may_day">
  <item name="av.may_day.header"><![CDATA[May Day in Skyrama!]]></item>
  <item name="av.may_day.title"><![CDATA[Things are heating up in the summer skies of Skyrama! Time to sip on a cocktail and party in the sand!]]></item>
  <item name="av.may_day.text"><![CDATA[Oh what a wonderful may!  The tower is bumping while we ring in the spring! Use the festive coinage to unlock exclusive items and celebrate Mother's Day, Father's Day and Spring Break all in one fell swoop. Now let's hope the turbulence stays away from the runway!]]></item>
  <item name="av.may_day.hint_title"><![CDATA[Let your coins do the talking]]></item>
  <item name="av.may_day.hint_text"><![CDATA[Get out and start collecting! The more coins you have, the more items you'll get!]]></item>
  <item name="av.may_day.shop_title"><![CDATA[Shopping fever!]]></item>
  <item name="av.may_day.shop_text"><![CDATA[Spring sale! Everything must go!]]></item>
 </category>
 <category name="av.eng_bay">
  <item name="av.eng_bay.header"><![CDATA[The engineering bay]]></item>
  <item name="av.eng_bay.title"><![CDATA[It's pretty bangin': Fine-tuning for your fleet!]]></item>
  <item name="av.eng_bay.text"><![CDATA[The brand new engineering bay is now available in the Airside Buildings section of the shop. In the new engineering bay, you can turbo-tune your entire fleet with parts from around the world. Upgrade your airplanes and ramacopter with new navigation systems, extra cargo room and better turbines. For just 100 aircoins you can get your own tuning hub. Factory-equipped planes are out; custom-made planes are in!]]></item>
  <item name="av.eng_bay.hint_title"><![CDATA[It's tuning time!]]></item>
  <item name="av.eng_bay.hint_text"><![CDATA[Now every 24 hours: Scrap planes for free!]]></item>
  <item name="av.eng_bay.shop_title"><![CDATA[From jets to sets]]></item>
  <item name="av.eng_bay.shop_text"><![CDATA[No time to collect parts? Get part sets in the shop at astronomically low prices!]]></item>
  <item name="av.eng_bay.buy_title"><![CDATA[Don't be afreight]]></item>
  <item name="av.eng_bay.buy_text"><![CDATA[Place tech-decorations next to bays to reduce their service time by max. 40%.]]></item>
  <item name="av.eng_bay.skin_title"><![CDATA[Hull-abaloo]]></item>
  <item name="av.eng_bay.skin_text"><![CDATA[Pretty-up your plane! Revamp your flyer and go the extra mile!]]></item>
 </category>
 <category name="av.announcement">
  <item name="av.announcement.header"><![CDATA[The Skyrama Herald]]></item>
  <item name="av.announcement.title"><![CDATA[Get a glimpse of tomorrow, today! Find out here first, what's about to happen next!]]></item>
  <item name="av.announcement.text"><![CDATA[It's tourist season and things are flying sky-high in Skyrama. We have a huge event lined up come month's end for aspiring and established athletes alike. Exclusive airplanes, brand-new buildings and lot's more will make the sun shine like gold. Furthermore, we're revamping everything behind the scenes by calling back the best team of exterminators we have in the hive to snuff out the jive of the latest bugs and stuff.]]></item>
  <item name="av.announcement.hint_title"><![CDATA[Bosom Buddies]]></item>
  <item name="av.announcement.hint_text"><![CDATA[Better, quicker, easier! The brand new invite feature will soon be go for launch.]]></item>
  <item name="av.announcement.shop_title"><![CDATA[Old and gray was for yesterday.]]></item>
  <item name="av.announcement.shop_text"><![CDATA[Daily quests like you've never seen before - coming soon!]]></item>
 </category>
 <category name="av.friends">
  <item name="av.friends.header"><![CDATA[Social Flightwork]]></item>
  <item name="av.friends.title"><![CDATA[Get a complete overview of all air traffic with the new Buddy Plan!]]></item>
  <item name="av.friends.text"><![CDATA[As an airport manager, you need to stay in close contact with your friends - otherwise, they forget about you and that's detrimental to business. Our ground crew told us about the problems you've been having with your online status and we've been working to fix them, so don't throw in the towel just yet. We've developed a new flight signal that will allow you to coordinate your flight plans with your Buddies! Just click the tower symbol in the upper left of the menu bar and, for the next 30 minutes, your name will be at the top of your friends' Buddy List. This will let them know that you can receive flights. What are you waiting for? Give it a try and let your partners know that you're ready for business!]]></item>
  <item name="av.friends.hint_title"><![CDATA[Updates:]]></item>
  <item name="av.friends.hint_text"><![CDATA[Place tech-decorations next to bays to reduce their service time by a max. of 40%.]]></item>
  <item name="av.friends.shop_title"><![CDATA[Stay for a while!]]></item>
  <item name="av.friends.shop_text"><![CDATA[Make yourself at home! Soon your passengers will be staying for 5 days in the terminal.]]></item>
 </category>
 <category name="av.10mi">
  <item name="av.10mi.header"><![CDATA[10 million registered users!]]></item>
  <item name="av.10mi.title"><![CDATA[We're popping bottles in Skyrama! A modest celebration to mark an important milestone!]]></item>
  <item name="av.10mi.text"><![CDATA[To show our thanks, we'll be giving you 5 free spins on the Lucky Luggage, 10 units of Super Fuel and parts for your engineering bay. Also, check out the shop for exclusive decorations and the Lofty MillionAir X. Set your course for the Millions Event! ]]></item>
  <item name="av.10mi.hint_title"><![CDATA[New beginnings are a breeze]]></item>
  <item name="av.10mi.hint_text"><![CDATA[10 million players, 1 week-long party - we'll be celebrating from December 10th, 2012 until the 17th!]]></item>
  <item name="av.10mi.shop_title"><![CDATA[Once upon a time ...]]></item>
  <item name="av.10mi.shop_text"><![CDATA[Croydon Airport, the world's first international airport, opened its gates in March of 1920.]]></item>
 </category>
 <category name="av.dark_orbit">
  <item name="av.dark_orbit.header"><![CDATA[Dark Airport: Visitors from deep space!]]></item>
  <item name="av.dark_orbit.title"><![CDATA[There future has arrived ... and it turns we don't need airplanes any more.]]></item>
  <item name="av.dark_orbit.text"><![CDATA[Breaking news! Goliath, the mighty battlecruiser, will be making a guest appearance at your airport within the next few hours. Get this flying fortress for your fleet to teach the competition a thing or two and show everyone that air traffic is headed for outer space ...]]></item>
  <item name="av.dark_orbit.hint_title"><![CDATA[Huge, hulking spaceships are the new black!]]></item>
  <item name="av.dark_orbit.hint_text"><![CDATA[6 years of DarkOrbit - this deep space adventure got its start on December 11th]]></item>
  <item name="av.dark_orbit.shop_title"><![CDATA[One-time offer]]></item>
  <item name="av.dark_orbit.shop_text"><![CDATA[It's now or never - don't miss the chance to own your own Goliath!]]></item>
 </category>
 <category name="av.high_level">
  <item name="av.high_level.header"><![CDATA[Landing Permission for High Flyers]]></item>
  <item name="av.high_level.title"><![CDATA[Our new high fliers have arrived!]]></item>
  <item name="av.high_level.text"><![CDATA[Why should you settle for flying high, when you could go to the very top? Soon, you'll be able to expand your fleet with the crème de la crème of international air transportation. Which legendary fliers will be the next to grace your airport? You'll have to wait and see!]]></item>
  <item name="av.high_level.hint_title"><![CDATA[Luck Be a Lady]]></item>
  <item name="av.high_level.hint_text"><![CDATA[Want to get your hands on some big wins? The jackpot's waiting!]]></item>
  <item name="av.high_level.shop_title"><![CDATA[Take off]]></item>
  <item name="av.high_level.shop_text"><![CDATA[The new planes - in stock and ready to go.]]></item>
 </category>
 <category name="av.newquests">
  <item name="av.newquests.header"><![CDATA[Quest-O-Rama]]></item>
  <item name="av.newquests.title"><![CDATA[Make way for New Missions!]]></item>
  <item name="av.newquests.text"><![CDATA[New stories, new characters, and a whole of exciting challenges! In the coming weeks, there's going to be a lot going on at the airport. After quite a long break from the main and story quests, Tariq,  Lin and friends are back and ready to mix things up at the airport. This week alone, we'll be releasing 10 new missions for all players, who have made their way through  their quest lists. More will be coming in the next few weeks. Loads more! Keep an eye out for new quest updates and the other things we have in store!]]></item>
  <item name="av.newquests.hint_title"><![CDATA[New Buildings in the Shop]]></item>
  <item name="av.newquests.hint_text"><![CDATA[There's something for everyone, whether you're looking for a wave machine or a security device.]]></item>
  <item name="av.newquests.shop_title"><![CDATA[WonderQuicky!]]></item>
  <item name="av.newquests.shop_text"><![CDATA[Collect plane parts to complete the WonderQuicky collection!!!]]></item>
 </category>
 <category name="av.recyclingnews">
  <item name="av.recyclingnews.header"><![CDATA[Scrap-Tastic: Recycle Your Planes!]]></item>
  <item name="av.recyclingnews.title"><![CDATA[From plain old to new planes!]]></item>
  <item name="av.recyclingnews.text"><![CDATA[The runway is jammed, the hangar is bursting and your flight crew is seething with rage ? Doesn't matter! From now on, you can easily clean up your airport, dispose of spare planes in the shiny new Recycling Center and gain some rare engine parts in return. Jet over to the Construction Hall, hand them to our smartest mechanics and have the plane of your dreams assembled right in front of your eyes. The future starts today. Ready for take-off?]]></item>
  <item name="av.recyclingnews.hint_title"><![CDATA[New parts]]></item>
  <item name="av.recyclingnews.hint_text"><![CDATA[Glas, bolts, metal and more: Get your spare parts, while they are hot!]]></item>
  <item name="av.recyclingnews.shop_title"><![CDATA[The Jet Set]]></item>
  <item name="av.recyclingnews.shop_text"><![CDATA[Lightning fast and super smooth: Show some style with your new planes!]]></item>
 </category>
</language>
