<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<language>
 <category name="av.goal">
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.14.name"><![CDATA[High Life!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.14.hint"><![CDATA[Hi my name is Tariq, your hotshot pilot. Together we will conquer the skies and see the world! Being your airport's most visible representative, I need to keep up appearances. Get me some smart watches and snazzy ties.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.14.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Cool! These ties and watches look top notch. Now I will look as dapper and smart as all the other pilots. That should impress them.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.14.CollectSouvenir.1.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} tie(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.14.CollectSouvenir.2.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} watch/watches]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.14.AddBuddy.name"><![CDATA[Add {number} buddy/Buddies]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.15.name"><![CDATA[Say It With Flowers]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.15.hint"><![CDATA[Hello my name is Lin, your stewardess. Keeping passengers happy is essential, a fact that some of my colleagues often ignore - especially that show-off Tariq. Your airport needs brightening up. I think flowers should do the trick.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.15.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Thank you! Your airport is looking much brighter and friendlier now. Appearances are very important in this business - investing in decorations will increase your passenger flow. But enough small talk I have paying passengers to charm.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.15.BuyLandsideBuilding.44.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} flowerbox/flowerboxes]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.15.BuyLandsideBuilding.8.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} flowerbox/flowerboxes]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.15.CollectSouvenir.15.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} flower(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.16.name"><![CDATA[Carbon Offset]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.16.hint"><![CDATA[So you're the new kid, huh? The name's Kurt, I keep the planes running. You and I will get along fine, so long as you help me do my job right. We need some serious amounts of greenage to offset our airport's carbon footprint. Go green.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.16.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Not bad. You just did your bit for the environment by placing all that lovely greenery. That will make Fiona, our air traffic controller, very happy. She takes this environmental stuff seriously.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.16.CollectSouvenir.11.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} newspaper(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.16.BuyLandsideBuilding.15.name"><![CDATA[Place {number} Bushy Tree(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.16.BuyLandsideBuilding.14.name"><![CDATA[Place {number} Pine Tree(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.17.name"><![CDATA[Pilot Club]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.17.hint"><![CDATA[If you want us to be respected, I need to become a member of the pilot's club. Should be a breeze - we just have to achieve high volume of plane traffic, and deliver some quality french cheese. If the pilots are impressed they will reward us with the coolest racer plane you've ever seen.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.17.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Now we're talking! The pilots were so impressed with how we handled such a high volume of flights that they rewarded us with an exclusive racer plane. You can show this beauty off at other airports and get some nice XP bonuses in the bargain. Awesome.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.17.CollectSouvenir.3.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} french cheese(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.17.SendPlane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.17.ReturnPlane.name"><![CDATA[Return {number} flight(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.17.VisitBuddy.name"><![CDATA[Visit {number} different airport(s) and collect passengers]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.18.name"><![CDATA[On The Go]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.18.hint"><![CDATA[Hello again. My passengers have been complaining about your airport - they say travelling to and from the airport is annoyingly slow. My passengers are busy people and don't like waiting around - do something to remedy the situation.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.18.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[More buses and taxis are just what my passengers ordered! Not to mention, they will increase your passenger flow. The postcards were a nice touch, maybe someday I can take a vacation and meet some friends who will like to get them.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.18.BuyLandsideBuilding.1.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} parking lot(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.18.BuyLandsideBuilding.4.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} bus station(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.18.BuyLandsideBuilding.2.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} taxi rank(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.18.CollectSouvenir.10.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} postcard(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.19.name"><![CDATA[Family Visit]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.19.hint"><![CDATA[Back already? Great! Can you help us out some more? Fiona's family are visiting the airport and I know she's anxious - not that she'd ever admit it. We need things are running efficiently now more than ever. Make sure to collect a lot of teddy bears to keep the children happy!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.19.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Not bad, kid. Fiona's family were impressed by the airport's smooth running. Hm, she looks so pretty when she's happy... What are you staring at? I think she's an impressive air traffic controller, that's all.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.19.ReturnPlane.name"><![CDATA[Return {number} flight(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.19.GetPassengers.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} passenger(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.19.CollectSouvenir.13.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} teddy bear(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.19.SellProducts.name"><![CDATA[Sell {number} product(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.20.name"><![CDATA[Flashy Racer]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.20.hint"><![CDATA[Hi! The pilot club rejected my application for membership. They said I lacked experience and maturity - as if! We'll show those elitist windbags. Nothing says experienced and mature like a flashy plane. Let's beat some performance targets to win an exclusive racer plane.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.20.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Cool! You won us a racer plane, awesome. We can fly this to all your Buddies and make them envious. Everyone knows that the Gee Bee is a very exclusive plane and something to brag about. That should show those windbags at the pilot club.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.20.ReturnPlane.21.name"><![CDATA[Return {number} Rama-XS-Turbo]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.20.SendPlane.19.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-XS-Quickie]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.21.name"><![CDATA[Essential Supplies]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.21.hint"><![CDATA[Hello. My passengers are happy for now - zero complaints but I wish I could be the same... I am so busy working I never have time to go shopping, and no friends to do it on my behalf. Could you help me collect some essential supplies?]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.21.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Thank you! I guess this makes us friends... These supplies are essential for keeping me looking fresh faced and elegant, an important part of passenger relations.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.21.CollectSouvenir.8.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} jewel(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.21.CollectSouvenir.5.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} shoe(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.21.CollectSouvenir.6.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} lipstick(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.21.CollectSouvenir.7.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} handbag(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.22.name"><![CDATA[New Standards]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.22.hint"><![CDATA[Hurry! We have to get cracking! Our airport is heading for bigger things and this requires meeting a whole new set of exacting standards. Gonna be stressful - to keep our stress levels in check pickup some snowglobes. I find them very calming.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.22.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Good work, kid. You've raised our game and demonstrated that we can meet exacting standards of service. Maybe you're not as useless as I first thought. I start to see why Fiona talks so highly of you.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.22.PlaceBay.3.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} medium bay(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.22.ReturnPlane.name"><![CDATA[Return {number} medium buddy plane(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.22.SendPlane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} medium plane(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.22.CollectSouvenir.9.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} snowglobe(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.23.name"><![CDATA[Love Is In The Air]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.23.hint"><![CDATA[Hi! The pilot club might not like me, but maybe the ladies will. Time for a charm offensive, lets try some romantic visits, bearing perfume.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.23.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[You rock! The ladies loved our charm offensive.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.23.SendPlane.1.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} flight(s) to Austria]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.23.SendPlane.13.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} flight(s) to France]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.23.SendPlane.7.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} flight(s) to Italy]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.23.CollectSouvenir.16.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} perfume(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.24.name"><![CDATA[Sweet Dreams]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.24.hint"><![CDATA[Hello. My passengers are getting tired from all the flying and need a comfortable night's sleep in a tranquil environment. See if you can set that up for me and try and collect some candies to keep them sweet.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.24.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Thank you so much! My passengers are much more relaxed after a good night's sleep.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.24.BuyLandsideBuilding.21.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} small hotel(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.24.CollectSouvenir.14.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} candy/candies]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.24.PlaceDecoration.19.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} Mixed Copse(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.25.name"><![CDATA[Cargo Pressure]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.25.hint"><![CDATA[Ready for some cargo crunching? If we run an efficient cargo chain, helping ourselves and our Buddies, then we get a free upgrade to our warehouse capacity. This gain is worth any pain.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.25.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Smart move, kid. Running an efficient cargo chain has helped you and your Buddies maximise your profits. This means you get a free upgrade to your warehouse capacity. That's a generous reward - it normally costs AirCash.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.25.SellProducts.name"><![CDATA[Sell {number} product(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.25.SendPlane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.25.SendPlane.20.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-XS-Cargo]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.25.SendPlane.27.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-M-Cargo]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.26.name"><![CDATA[Pilot Club Racer]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.26.hint"><![CDATA[Hi! The pilot club have been in touch. They are reconsidering my application. We can't afford to mess this up. I need to prove my maturity and experience with some serious flight stats. The prize is membership of the pilot club and an exclusive racer.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.26.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Groovy! The pilot club say your flight statistics prove our maturity and experience. We are in the club! On a provisional basis. That means we get our hands on an exclusive racer, another plane to show-off at your Buddies' airports.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.26.SendPlane.25.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-M-Turbo]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.26.SendPlane.29.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-M-SuperTurbo]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.26.SendPlane.27.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-M-Cargo]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.27.name"><![CDATA[Mass Transit]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.27.hint"><![CDATA[Hello. Your airport is getting big but you need to take care. Passenger numbers are rising and you need to make sure you can handle them all. You should make some large scale improvements to transporation and accomodation.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.27.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Thank you so much! My passengers are buzzing about your airport's large-scale improvements. You are heading for the big league]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.27.BuyLandsideBuilding.21.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} small hotel(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.27.PlaceLandsideBuilding.3.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} Multi- Storey Parking(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.27.CollectSouvenir.12.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} gift(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.28.name"><![CDATA[Contingency Planning]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.28.hint"><![CDATA[You think everything's running smoothly right? Think again. You have built up an efficient airport but one hiccup could put a spanner in the works. I want you to prove to me that our airport has backups to cope with any emergency.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.28.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Nicely done, kid. Our airport has the ability to soak up whatever is thrown at us. I feel you are ready for the bigger challenges that lie ahead.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.28.BuyLandsideBuilding.31.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} medium fuel depot(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.28.CollectSouvenir.21.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} radar(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.28.CollectSouvenir.23.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} windsock(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.28.CollectSouvenir.22.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} coffeemachine(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.70.name"><![CDATA[Streamline]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.70.hint"><![CDATA[For us air traffic controllers the airport has become quite big, to keep an overview some streamlining is necessary. Put objects into your storage, place some streets and try to get all those cars away from the airport!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.70.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Thank you so much! It's a lot better now. The airport is more streamlined, giving me a much better overview.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.70.BuyLandsideBuilding.27.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} small street part(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.70.BuyLandsideBuilding.3.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} Multi-Storey Parking(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.70.StoreLandsideBuilding.name"><![CDATA[Use your storage]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.71.name"><![CDATA[Unimpressed Stewardess]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.71.hint"><![CDATA[You know my friend, there is this stewardess... No-one you know, of course... She remains unimpressed by my feats of piloting. Perhaps some luxury french gifts will do the trick.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.71.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Wonderful! There was a twinkle in her eyes, I'm the greatest! Now she recognizes what a great romantic fantastic wonderful..  man and pilot i am.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.71.SendPlane.13.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s) to France]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.71.SendPlane.22.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s) to Switzerland]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.71.CollectSouvenir.12.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} gift(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.71.CollectSouvenir.8.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} jewel(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.72.name"><![CDATA[Flyby Marketing]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.72.hint"><![CDATA[Our airport needs to raise its fame, put itself on the map. Let's do some marketing and send out some charming flybys!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.72.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Great! I was invited into the VIP area at the last 3 airports I visited. We should keep sending those flybys.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.72.SendPlane.34.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} flyby(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.72.SendPlane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} medium plane(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.72.ReturnPlane.name"><![CDATA[Return {number} medium plane(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.73.name"><![CDATA[Ramacopter Training]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.73.hint"><![CDATA[Hey, We need a training Ramacopter for several reasons, the service chain isn't working perfect and also groundstaff experiences some problems with the bays.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.73.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Not bad! The new Ramacopter helps us train our service chain and improve our work with Ramacopters]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.73.BuyPlane.3.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} Ramacopter-Steady]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.73.SendPlane.3.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Ramacopter-Steady]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.73.SendPlane.2.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Ramacopter-Quickie]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.74.name"><![CDATA[Quick Landing]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.74.hint"><![CDATA[A lot of people from other airports are watching us because of our Ramacopter investments. To impress them a bit more we should buy an additional Ramacopter bay. It doesn't look good if Ramacopter passengers have to wait forever until they can leave the Ramacopter or start with boarding.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.74.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[So nice! Finally the waiting loop for Ramacopters has decreased noticebly. Thanks kido!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.74.BuyBay.7.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} Ramacopter bay(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.74.CollectSouvenir.21.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} Radar(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.74.SendPlane.2.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Ramacopter-Quickie]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.75.name"><![CDATA[The Great Outdoors]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.75.hint"><![CDATA[Hey, It's me again, Kurt. You know my grandsons they love the airport and they would really like to spend their holiday here next to their hardworking grandpa. But the hotel alone is not enough they want to go hiking. Can't you organize me some of those hiking souvenirs?]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.75.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Thanks so much, sir! I'm looking foward to showing my proud grandsons the airport and the natural beauty of its surroundings!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.75.BuyLandsideBuilding.60.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} habitat wood(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.75.CollectSouvenir.29.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} raincoat(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.75.CollectSouvenir.28.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} rucksack(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.76.name"><![CDATA[Showing-Off]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.76.hint"><![CDATA[We need to keep the pilots club impressed don't we? I would suggest we send out some impressive jets to show them all what we've got.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.76.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Good news! It looks like the pilots club are impressed by your fleet, and your ever so humble pilot.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.76.SendPlane.29.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-M-Super-Turbo]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.76.SendPlane.3.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Ramacopter-Steady]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.76.SendPlane.34.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Flyby(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.77.name"><![CDATA[Bugs And Burns]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.77.hint"><![CDATA[The whole airport is under attack by mosquitos. We need some bug sprays and sun cream for our workers. It's time to invest some money into the airport crew's equipment!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.77.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Nice job, the crew is very happy about the investments! Thank you.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.77.GetAirCoins.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} AirCoin(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.77.CollectSouvenir.26.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} sunscreen(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.77.CollectSouvenir.31.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} bugspray(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.78.name"><![CDATA[Big Footie Match]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.78.hint"><![CDATA[It's the finals! We should collect all the fans from the different airports, stuff them into medium passenger planes and fly them to Great Britain! This is going to be the game of the games!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.78.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[What a great final! The people really enjoyed the game and their stay in England, we should do that next time again!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.78.SendPlane.23.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} medium plane(s) to Great Britain]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.78.SendPlane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} small plane(s) to Great Britain]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.78.VisitBuddy.name"><![CDATA[Visit {number} airport(s) to collect passengers]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.79.name"><![CDATA[The Inspectors]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.79.hint"><![CDATA[Inspectors are on their way! We should train our groundstaff so that we easily pass the inspections with an A++. I'd suggest to service some Ramacopter-Turbo and Rama-XS-Quickie.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.79.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Well done, looks very promising now! The inspectors can visit us whenever they want. That's motivating!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.79.SendPlane.2.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Ramacopter-Quickie]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.79.SendPlane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} medium plane(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.79.SendPlane.34.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Flyby(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.79.SendPlane.19.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-XS-Quickie]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.80.name"><![CDATA[Prickly Welcome]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.80.hint"><![CDATA[Why not enrich the airport with some exotic plants? I'm sure our passengers will appreciate it.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.80.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[How sweet, the kids love the new cactus. We should keep an eye on decorations and passengers.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.80.GetPassengers.name"><![CDATA[Get {number} passenger(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.80.BuyLandsideBuilding.50.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} cactus/cacti]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.80.SendPlane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.81.name"><![CDATA[Cargo Crush]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.81.hint"><![CDATA[There are a lot of airports out there who could send us some cargo, let's put some pressure on our cargo teams so that we can earn a lot more money by selling products.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.81.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Haven't I told you - earning money is a nice thing! And the positive side effect of servicing cargo planes are lots of happy and reliable cargo Buddies.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.81.SellProducts.name"><![CDATA[Sell {number} products]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.81.ReturnPlane.27.name"><![CDATA[Service and return {number} Rama-M-Cargo]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.81.SendPlane.20.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-XS-Cargo]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.82.name"><![CDATA[Trekking Crew]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.82.hint"><![CDATA[The crew organized some hiking weekends, to improve team morale. Let's help them along with some special supplies!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.82.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Great! The crew are super-motivated now. Although they are a bit tired from all the trekking. Luckily the coffee will pick them up.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.82.CollectSouvenir.22.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} coffemachine(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.82.CollectSouvenir.30.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} compass/compasses]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.82.CollectSouvenir.31.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} bugspray(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.82.CollectSouvenir.24.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} walkingboot(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.83.name"><![CDATA[Famously Fantastic]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.83.hint"><![CDATA[Hey, It's me again. I know we are quite well-known out there but why not aim higher? Let's decorate our airport with something fantastic and send some flyby planes to raise our visibility.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.83.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Cool! The giant cockerel really attracted attention and praise, along with all our friendly flybys. Everybody is buzzing about us!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.83.SendPlane.34.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Flyby(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.83.SendPlane.32.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} 1930s Racer Hughes]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.83.SendPlane.31.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} 1930s Racer Gee Bee]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.83.BuyLandsideBuilding.52.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} giant flying cockerel(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.84.name"><![CDATA[The Seaking Challenge]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.84.hint"><![CDATA[Unbelievable! There's this new pilot at the club bragging about his Ramacopter-Seaking skills. I'll show him! Let me put in some hours and polish my skills.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.84.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Ha! All that extra practice paid off. The new guy saw my skills and quit with his bragging. There's only room for one hotshot loudmouth at the pilot club- and that's me!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.84.SendPlane.4.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Ramacopter-Seaking]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.84.SendPlane.2.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Ramacopter-Quickie]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.84.SendPlane.3.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Ramacopter-Steadie]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.85.name"><![CDATA[The Globetrotter]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.85.hint"><![CDATA[I want to see more of the world. After all, variety is the spice of life. Let's fly to countries off the beaten track. I am sure the routes will prove popular.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.85.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Wow, thanks!!! The new experience revived my enthusiasm about being a stewardess and flying the world.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.85.SendPlane.55.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} medium plane(s) to Cyprus]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.85.SendPlane.43.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} medium plane(s) to Macedonia]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.85.SendPlane.39.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s) to Bosnia and Herzegovina]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.85.SendPlane.44.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s) to Estonia]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.86.name"><![CDATA[Keeping Up Appearances]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.86.hint"><![CDATA[Our airport is at risk of looking a bit unfashionable. We need to stay ahead of the decoration trends. Climbing plants are going to be all the rage. Get some planted, and keep an eye on who's falling behind in the decoration stakes.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.86.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Not bad, the climbing plants look ultra-fashionable. Just look at all the trendy couples posing in front of them. It's always important to keep up appearances.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.86.BuyLandsideBuilding.61.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} Flower Arches]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.86.SendPlane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} plane(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.86.SendPlane.34.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Flyby(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.87.name"><![CDATA[Money Money Money!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.87.hint"><![CDATA[Markets are turbulent and investors are getting nervous. Build up a large reserve of money to calm their jittery nerves.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.87.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Loads of money! That should calm our investors and keep us flying. Well done!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.87.GetAirCoins.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} Aircoin(s)]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.106.name"><![CDATA[Around The World]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.106.hint"><![CDATA[Fiona always says a real pilot knows the whole world. I know it's much to ask but couldn't you get me some exotic souvenirs? I'm sure that would impress her!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.106.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Hurray! Today Fiona held the elevator when she saw me coming! I think your souvenirs really impressed her.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.106.CollectSouvenir.36.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} flip flops]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.106.CollectSouvenir.37.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} cameras]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.106.CollectSouvenir.34.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} swimm shorts]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.106.CollectSouvenir.33.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} sunglasses]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.107.name"><![CDATA[Tourists!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.107.hint"><![CDATA[This year several holidays all fall on the coming week! Expect a real stampede of tourists.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.107.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[All turned out well and we made a lot of coins with those customers.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.107.SendPlane.104.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} medium planes to Kentucky]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.107.SendPlane.126.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} medium planes to Florida]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.107.SendPlane.93.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} medium planes to Texas]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.107.SendPlane.80.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} medium planes to Nevada]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.108.name"><![CDATA[Action Holiday]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.108.hint"><![CDATA[Hi! I'm Cassandra your new seaplane pilot. There are some really exciting destinations that can only be reached by seaplanes or helicopters. But people would love them I'm sure!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.108.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[See! It's a little hard to get there but it's definitely worth it!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.108.BuyLandsideBuilding.68.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} Skydancer]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.108.SendPlane.seaplane.sa.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} seaplanes to South America]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.108.SendPlane.helicopter.na.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} helicopters to North America]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.108.SendPlane.plane.eu.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to Europe]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.109.name"><![CDATA[Mp3 Batteries]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.109.hint"><![CDATA[Can you believe it! The batteries of my Mp3 player are empty after only 3 long distance flights. I can't fly without my music! Please get me new ones.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.109.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Great! Where did you manage to find those? I hope it wasn't too much trouble to get them.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.109.SendPlane.27.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-M-Cargo to California]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.109.SendPlane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.109.CollectSouvenir.40.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} batteries]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.109.CollectSouvenir.39.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} mp3players]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.110.name"><![CDATA[Heli-Trip]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.110.hint"><![CDATA[Well I heard that our new pilot can fly seaplanes. But can she also handle a helicopter? Let's find out.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.110.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Pretty impressive! She landed those helicopters like she grew up in one!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.110.SendPlane.34.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} flybys]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.110.SendPlane.helicopter.eu.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} helicopters to Europe]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.110.SendPlane.helicopter.na.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} helicopters to North America]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.110.ReturnPlane.helicopter.name"><![CDATA[Return {number} helicopters]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.111.name"><![CDATA[Waterpilot]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.111.hint"><![CDATA[Did you see how that Australian girl landed that seaplane!  If I could impress her surely Fiona would get jealous! At least it's worth a try.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.111.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[I'm not sure if that worked out the way I planned it. I just saw Fiona and the new girl giggling about something in the cafeteria.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.111.SendPlane.10.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} SeaRama-Amphib]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.111.SendPlane.13.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} SeaRama-XL-Aqua]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.111.SendPlane.11.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} SeaRama-Solo]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.111.SendPlane.12.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} SeaRama-Clipper]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.112.name"><![CDATA[The crew challenge]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.112.hint"><![CDATA[I don't like how Cassandra is getting all of Fionas attention these days. I will show her who the best pilot on that airport is!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.112.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Well, she might have been quicker than me but you must agree that my flyby had a lot more style!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.112.SendPlane.34.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} flyby]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.112.SendPlane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.113.name"><![CDATA[Waterpilot On Ice]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.113.hint"><![CDATA[Great! Now Casandra and Fiona don't talk to me anymore! We'll need something big to change their minds about me.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.113.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Ha! That giant bear was just the thing! No girl can resist such a thing.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.113.CollectSouvenir.12.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} Gifts]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.113.CollectSouvenir.16.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} Perfumes]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.113.BuyLandsideBuilding.69.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} Flying Heart]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.113.BuyLandsideBuilding.53.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} Flying Bear]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.114.name"><![CDATA[Holiday outfit]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.114.hint"><![CDATA[Cassandra invited me and all the others to visit her in Australia! Fiona will be coming to! I need to look as sharp as possible for that trip.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.114.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Ah that was just what I needed! This time there's no way Fiona can ignore me!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.114.CollectSouvenir.35.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} Bikinis]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.114.CollectSouvenir.33.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} Sunglasses]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.114.CollectSouvenir.34.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} Swimm Shorts]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.114.CollectSouvenir.36.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} Flip Flops]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.115.name"><![CDATA[Cargo]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.115.hint"><![CDATA[We are lacking cargo for the upcoming season. We should get some new stuff and sell out the old wares.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.115.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[A job well done! We are all set for the next season.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.115.SellProducts.name"><![CDATA[Sell {number} products]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.115.SendPlane.20.sa.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-XS-Cargo to South America]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.115.SendPlane.27.eu.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-M-Cargo to Europe]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.116.name"><![CDATA[Water-visit]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.116.hint"><![CDATA[Hey there! I invited some of my pilot colleagues to hop by on their next trip. Of course they will bring some customers with them as well.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.116.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Thanks for helping me out. It was nice seeing them again!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.116.SendPlane.34.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} flyby]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.116.SendPlane.seaplane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Seaplanes]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.116.ReturnPlane.seaplane.name"><![CDATA[Return {number} Seaplanes]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.117.name"><![CDATA[Heli- visit]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.117.hint"><![CDATA[Cassandra thinks she's the only one with old friends ha! I will organize a meeting of the best heli pilots out there!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.117.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Ha that showed her! Strange that they all seemed to know her a lot better than me though.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.117.SendPlane.34.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} flyby]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.117.SendPlane.helicopter.eu.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} helicopters to Europe]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.117.SendPlane.helicopter.na.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} helicopters to North America]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.117.SendPlane.helicopter.sa.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} helicopters to South America]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.118.name"><![CDATA[Camera]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.118.hint"><![CDATA[I promised Fiona I would lend her my camera for her next trip. The thing is I don't actually have one. Could you get me camera plus batteries?]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.118.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Thank you! You really are a life saver.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.118.CollectSouvenir.37.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} Cameras]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.118.CollectSouvenir.40.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} Batteries]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.119.name"><![CDATA[Speedy Servicer]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.119.hint"><![CDATA[Let's see how quickly we can service the incoming planes with all our new equipment!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.119.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Wow! All our staff is impressed by your organization skills!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.119.SendPlane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} small planes]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.119.SendPlane.plane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.119.SendPlane.seaplane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} seaplanes]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.119.SendPlane.helicopter.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} helicopters]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.120.name"><![CDATA[Airshow]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.120.hint"><![CDATA[Why not bring out some of our classic planes for a little airshow. People always like to see those oldies.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.120.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[See! People loved our airshow! Don't forget your roots with all that fancy new stuff.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.120.SendPlane.32.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} 1930s Racer Hughes]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.120.SendPlane.35.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} 1930s Mr. Mulligan]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.120.SendPlane.31.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} 1930s GeeBees]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.121.name"><![CDATA[Souvenirs]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.121.hint"><![CDATA[My grandchildren are coming for a visit next week. The little ones always love teddies right? Could you get me some?]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.121.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Thank you. I think your help is the only reason I'm still their favorite grandfather.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.121.CollectSouvenir.13.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} Teddies]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.122.name"><![CDATA[Moneymaker]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.122.hint"><![CDATA[Those finance guys come up with a new crisis every month these days. Investors are nervous and want us to save some money for rainy days.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.122.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Excellent! That should keep our investors calm.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.122.GetAirCoins.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} AirCoins]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.419.name"><![CDATA[Scary Stories]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.419.hint"><![CDATA[Hi there! I have to say that all that talking about security made me a little nervous. Imagine the plane gets hit by a meteorite or an UFO! I definitely need one of those multi-tools, just in case.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.419.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Thanks you so much! I feel a lot safer already.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.419.CollectSouvenir.52.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} Multitools]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.419.SendPlane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.420.name"><![CDATA[Over The Top]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.420.hint"><![CDATA[I heard Lin is a little scared by all those new security measures. That’s understandable as she is no world class pilot like me. It might help her if I took her on my next flight.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.420.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[We got in to some turbulences and I’m not sure but from what Lin was telling me I might have blacked out for some minutes. Lin had to bring the bird down all by herself.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.420.SendPlane.73.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to Chile]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.420.SendPlane.147.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to Tasmania]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.420.CollectSouvenir.17.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} Globes]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.421.name"><![CDATA[Never again]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.421.hint"><![CDATA[I’ll never fly with Tariq again! Even thinking of that horrible flight gives me panic attacks! Could you get me some more safety tools! It would make me feel so much better to have them around.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.421.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[O thank god! You really got them for me. I’m feeling better already.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.421.CollectSouvenir.48.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} Medi Kits]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.421.CollectSouvenir.50.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} Flashlights]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.421.SendPlane.helicopter.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} helicopters]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.422.name"><![CDATA[Spontaneous Combustion]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.422.hint"><![CDATA[I saw in last night X-News how a passenger’s luggage spontaneously caught fire! They say that can happen to any luggage any time when exposed to quick pressure change! I have to be prepared for this!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.422.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Thanks for the fire drencher. It just might safe my life one of these days.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.422.GetPassengers.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} Passengers]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.422.CollectSouvenir.51.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} Fire Extinguisher]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.422.SendPlane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.423.name"><![CDATA[Japanology]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.423.hint"><![CDATA[We met some potential investors from Japan who showed their interest in our airport. They will show us a visit soon. Let’s welcome them with some old school Japanese decorations. They will love that.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.423.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Perfect! Our visitors were pretty impressed of our well cut bonsais. I think they felt quite at home.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.423.PlaceLandsideBuilding.85.name"><![CDATA[Buy {number} Bonsai]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.423.SendPlane.189.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to Japan]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.426.name"><![CDATA[Permanent Vacation]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.426.hint"><![CDATA[We are doing pretty well with our modernization. I think it is time we rewarded ourselves with a nice little holiday. So pack your fishing rod and towel cause were flying to the beach!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.426.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Isn’t that one of the finest fishing spots ever! Thanks for making this possible boss.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.426.SendPlane.140.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to Jamaika]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.426.SendPlane.13.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to France]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.426.CollectSouvenir.36.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} Flip Flops]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.427.name"><![CDATA[Don't Worry]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.427.hint"><![CDATA[That Tariq really messed it up this time! Just being close to a planes or passengers terrifies Lin since her trip with him, and she is stewardess! I have to show her that flying is nothing to be afraid of.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.427.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[It seems that was quite a success. After seeing how smooth we took off Lin was very calm for the whole flight.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.427.SendPlane.66.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to Guyana]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.427.GetPassengers.name"><![CDATA[Collect {number} passengers]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.428.name"><![CDATA[Surf up]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.428.hint"><![CDATA[This beach here is pretty nice all right, but I heard the waves are currently in other spots. Grab your surf board we’re going for a ride!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.428.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[This is just great! Did you see me coming out that tunnel, oh man I just love surfing!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.428.SendPlane.76.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to Hawai]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.428.SendPlane.184.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to the Philippines]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.428.SendPlane.141.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to Victoria, Australia]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.429.name"><![CDATA[The Right Bait]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.429.hint"><![CDATA[It’s a nice fishing spot all right, but somehow those picky fish aren’t biting. The local fisherman say they are using some very rare baits from all kind of faraway places. Could you get me some of those?]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.429.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Well thanks for the effort. Tonight we’ll be dining grilled fish! You can count on that!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.429.SendPlane.232.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to Uganda]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.429.SendPlane.51.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to Sweden]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.430.name"><![CDATA[Out Of Here]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.430.hint"><![CDATA[Great! Now everyone knows I can’t swim, thanks to Fiona. She practically forced me in to steep water by doubting my swim skill. At least she dragged me out afterwards. Anyway, get me somewhere far away from here!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.430.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[That’s better! Those chilly nice mountains! What a sight, and no ocean nor lake anywhere to be seen. Just great!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.430.SendPlane.na.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} planes to North America]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.430.SellProducts.name"><![CDATA[Sell {number} products]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.431.name"><![CDATA[Campfire]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.431.hint"><![CDATA[Help! Please send some of our new fire fighter planes over here real quick! I was supposed to make a little campfire to grill the fish Kurt caught today, but I kind of set the camp on fire instead!]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.431.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Thanks for saving us! The fish is a little black, and so are our tents but nobody got hurt so I say let bygones be bygones and focus on tomorrow!]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.431.SendPlane.1053.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-FireFighter to Jamaica]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.431.SendPlane.seaplane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} seaplanes]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.432.name"><![CDATA[Baywatch]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.432.hint"><![CDATA[Do you think it’s possible that a grown man can’t swim? I find it a little suspicious that Tariq is staying in shallow water all the time. I better keep an eye on him.]]></item>
  <item name="av.goal.pilot.432.rewardMsg"><![CDATA[Guess I was right. When I confronted him he just shouted at me and ran off. Thank god that you sent those helicopters to look for him.]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.432.SendPlane.52.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} Rama-Ambulance to Florida]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.432.SendPlane.helicopter.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} helicopters]]></item>
  <item name="av.task.pilot.432.SendPlane.seaplane.name"><![CDATA[Send {number} seaplane]]></item>
 </category>
</language>
